Let's invite our Special Bomby Guest for today
Yes, today's guest is by all measures truly a top star
A super popular woman in her 20s
- In her 20s?
Since her teens she's been doing music, dramas, and CMs
She's very active
And in great demand
She is currently enjoying great popularity nationwide
- But she seems like someone who's always been popular
I wonder if she's ever had a "bomby" (poor) period?
She doesn't have that image
Probably nobody here would expect her to have a "poor" image
Tonight's Special Bomby Guest is...
- Sexy!
Someone who played the role of a detective in a TV drama
Also this year, she starred in her first musical of the Shakespeare play "Hamlet"
Actually this guest is also someone who sings
Last year was her 9th appearance in Kouhaku Uta Gassen
- That's amazing!
Performing before Fukuyama Masaharu, and after X-Japan
Without popularity and ability it would be impossible
to perform at such important positions
She's been in CMs for major food companies,
Job search sites, game consoles, and mobile phones
She's picked up various CMs
When we asked our guests about their impressions
- She is THE "Kokuminteki" (national-level)
That's my impression
- Did you know she used to be "bomby" (poor)?
- I don't see it
- Neither do I!
- She seems like a daughter of a rich family
- A rich kid?
She is someone who doesn't have a "bomby" impression at all!
She is a super popular artist in her 20s
The place this guest grew up in...
- Cute!
Has the highest production of figs in Japan
The figs are not only put in desserts
But also coated in miso to be eaten as dengaku
The production of succulent plants is also no.1 in Japan
It also has the highest number of people with surname "Kato"
It's Aichi prefecture!
We want to reveal the name of the city right now but
Previously, the guest mentioned on Instagram
"I'm currently at a filming here!"
And only with that...
Fans rushed to the location causing a large panic
So we won't reveal anything more!
Anyway, she is super popular right now but
Her house is super "bomby"...
When she went to her elementary school friend's house?
Here you go, enjoy the food!
- Thank you very much!
Waa~ it's luxurious!
I've never seen a meal like this before!
At her own house, however...
- Dinner's ready!
Okonomiyaki with nothing but cabbage
- That looks sad
"But, I'll just have to endure it"
The reason this guest thought that was
On the way back from school at the supermarket
She saw her mother buying
Nothing but clearance and discounted ingredients
The differences with others
weren't just limited to food
- Take your time and enjoy
- Thank you very much!
Wa~ It's so pretty
It smells good!
But at the guest's home...
[Dreary]
The only thing that was green was...
- Ja-jan!
Yes, this is it
Empty PET bottles reused and repurposed
To grow leftovers of
Bean sprouts!
- Wow, it's cute!
Not only that, we can eat it one more time!
Also...
Before realising it
The house was filled with edible plants
- That looks delicious
- Even with just a little green
I was able to become happy
In order to support the family
The guest's mother worked as an aesthetician
Often coming home late
At that time, all her classmates
Played games on the Nintendo DS, which was a hit at the time
But the thing that distracted the guest from her loneliness was
The brown body pillow she always hugged
And television
What she liked the most was
A show with young witch girls
Ojamajo doremi
"I want to wear cute clothes like this too!"
- I'm home!
I brought some clothes
- Yatta!
-Yes
But, they were hand-me-downs from a cousin in the neighbourhood
There were nothing but pants
Things like cute one-piece dresses
Or pink clothes
I wanted to wear things like that
But that didn't really happen
This guest
When she was in 5th grade
She experienced an impactful encounter
It was the NHK Kouhaku Utagassen on New Year's Eve
Aitakatta, aitakatta, aitakatta, yes!
Later on, the guest would perform on the same stage as them
It's AKB48!
"I want to be an idol too!"
"And then if I become famous"
"I can ease the burden on my mother"
While waiting for her new 6th grade term, there was this night...
Okaasan
- Hmm...?
I...
I want to become an idol
- Is that so?
Actually...
I wanted to be a singer too
- Eh?!
- But I gave up on it
To become an entertainer...
It requires a lot of money
Just as her mother described
Amuro Namie-san
(Okinawa Actors School)
Koda Kumi-san
(Toei Actors School)
Perfume, and others
(Actors School Hiroshima)
Artists in the forefront of the industry
Most of them came from talent training schools
To enter, the admission fee is 300,000 yen
Lesson fees are 20,000 yen per month
That amounts to 540,000 yen per year
As you can see, this requires a lot of money
- To become an idol
I didn't expect that it would need that much money
Two generations yearned to be in the entertainment industry
But, the money issues...
One day, this happened
- About the training school
It's okay to go!
- Eh?! Really?!
But Okaasan...
What about the money...?
- It will be fine!
Actually, the mother
In order to make the guest's dream come true
She did some additional work packaging contact lens
And also did some work delivering bread to homes
This was all to earn the money to go to the training school
This way, the guest was able to
enter a training school in her hometown in Aichi prefecture
To get the stamina necessary to continue with countless hours of intense training
During the break times...
- Today, I'm having a sandwich!
- It's a chocopan for me!
- Wow, the chocopan looks delicious!
There were kids who bought various things from convenience stores
A sandwich, a snack bread
A juice, and a snack
That amounts to nearly 1000 yen
That's why the guest brought this from home
Onigiri that her mother makes
"I have to be grateful to my mother"
"I need to work hard!"
But, she hadn't been able to reach out to any talent agencies
"I want to go for an audition"
"But... they're all in Tokyo"
”The transportation costs will be high"
”Going to Tokyo is impossible"
When she was about to give up
"Ah!"
"If it's this, I can go!"
In Nagoya, there was a big audition
Furthermore, it will be in Nagoya all the way until the final evaluation
The number of applicants was 2670
And among them...
- Yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
In the final evaluation, among 50 people
The guest who still remained sang this song
The mother who wanted to be a singer
Often sang this in karaoke
Koda Kumi's "Anytime"
She passed!
And then
3 months after passing the audition
She made her CD debut!
Not long after, she became very popular
But still, the guest...
- Here, it's 3000 yen today too
- Thank you!
Even after she turned 20
She's never seen her own paycheck
She leaves her salary to her mother
And receives an allowance
In the morning she would make onigiri
And with the napkin she's used since elementary school
She would wrap the onigiri and go to work
When she gets home
She would pass time by hugging the brown body pillow
The kitchen vegetable garden has also continued
Recently, even the seeds from peppers used in dishes were taken and planted
- That's amazing
- If there was anything I'd want to spend money on
It would be to renovate my grandmother's house
To make it easier to live in
After achieving success, certain celebrities would immediately
Live in a large mansion with a garden in the entrance
Or buy a luxury car worth over 10 million yen
But, in the case of our guest
For her grandmother to live easier
She aims to use the money to renovate her grandmother's old house
As of now, she has appeared in Kouhaku Uta Gassen 9 times
She acts in dramas
She picks up CMs left and right
A super popular artist in her 20s who is active in multiple fields
Have you already guessed who this guest might be?
- Well, the image I had of her was completely different
- Can I take a guess?
Could it be someone who has international fame?
- Oh?
- Is that alright?
- Yes, go ahead
Lady Gaga?
- Bean sprouts?!
- Which part of that was Lady Gaga?!
- Let's have our guest appear
It's this person!
- So that's who she was
- Today's Special Bomby Guest is this person!
It's SKE48's Matsui Jurina-san!
- Yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
- It's really unexpected
There's one thing we're all curious about
Are you still receiving an allowance?
- Yes, that's right
I let my mother manage my income
And there's that but
Because I'm now over 20, my mother said
Maybe it's good to at least look at the account book
- Up till then you've never even seen it even once?
- I'd never seen it
- How many years has it been accumulating?
- Around 10 years
- So you looked at it?
- Yes, I looked at it
- How was it?
- My reaction was...
"Mmm... I still need to work hard"
- Is that so?
- Yes
- Was it lower than expected?
- Really?
How much money was it?
How much?
- NG!