Matsui-chan, do you have any complaints?
- Complaints?
Ehh? Let's see...
Mariko-sama is someone who very clearly speaks her mind
Even to members
This is something she says especially to me
"Your clothes are ugly" -- she says that a lot
She just says it normally, like "it's ugly!"
She says it without hesitation at all
That's why, if she speaks her true mind like that
Sometimes I get a bit upset
But after that she'd take me out to buy some new clothes together
Even today, these are clothes I got from her
- Eh... it's cute!
Ah, so she gave it to you?
- Yes!
Because your clothes were ugly
- But really, when I say "it's ugly" it's...
Skulls, skulls, skulls
- Ehh? It's not skulls!!
She's an idol, after all
If fans see her like that
They might go "Eh.. Jurina is kind of...", and that isn't good
She has an image to keep after all
Skulls, skulls, skulls
Even her bag is skulls
- That's not true!!!
It's scary
- Well anyway, so that I'm not told that my clothes are ugly today
I'm wearing the clothes I got from her
- Yesterday she suddenly sent me a picture of this one-piece
"What goes well with this? What kind of shoes?"
I was wondering what that was about
And then she came here like this
"Ah, so that's what it was about"
- You didn't say anything about it did you?
That's right
- That was dangerous, you were so close to spoiling the surprise
I told her I was uploading it to my blog
But actually there was no meaning even if I chose good shoes
[The shoes are outside the room]