Everyone, good evening!
The Return of Jurina, "Privacy" edition is starting now! Yay!
I wonder if it's broadcasting properly...
Is anyone coming?
Are they coming- Oh they're here! Yay, thank you so much!
Oh, wow. Even before we started there are already 3600 viewers.
Amazing, thanks so much. I'm back!
For this episode, we're actually "borrowing" the title from a certain movie.
"The Return of XX"... there was a movie like that, wasn't there?
[Note: The Return of Ultraman]
So, this time we were allowed to plagiarise it from the movie
"Allowed to plagiarise" sounds so weird
Yabai! It's my first SHOWROOM in a long time
I'm really not even sure what I'm feeling right now.
I'm so nervous
I wonder if it's alright?
The comments feed isn't moving at all
There are comments saying "has it started yet?"
I'm really excited.
Anyway, this is a special livestream to commemorate my first solo album Privacy which went on sale on 5 Oct 2019.
I will be speaking at length to introduce the recorded songs as well as previously untold stories.
After that, in the later half of the stream, there will also be a new announcement regarding "Privacy"
So please watch until the end. Yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
So without further ado --
Oh wow, the comments!
There are also viewers from Korea.
"You're doing a Christmas show aren't you?" was written there.
There's about 2 weeks left till Christmas
The city's completely in Christmas mode, isn't it?
Looking at that, I felt like doing a little bit of cosplay
This is kind of like a Brown Santa?
When we think of Santa it's usually red isn't it?
But my hair colour is like this, so I thought the colours would match
Although it's a Santa-cosplay, I have reindeer antlers on my head
It's a jumbled up cosplay
Whether it's a reindeer cosplay, or really a santa cosplay,
we don't really know
It's a greedy santa.
So we're broadcasting Jurisanta to you today!
Without further ado...
Maybe I'll start with Privacy
Da-dum!
This is the artist photo.
This is actually without makeup, mostly.
Really, there was barely any-
If you zoom in that much it's embarrassing
This was taken when I was bare-faced
It was taken this well
For the jacket photo, I decided to use
some of my private photos up till now,
and arrange it this way.
So I'd thought that was actually rarer
But fans tell me, this one's better
They said they would've bought more if it were this one
Don't tell me sad things like that!
But I think my choice is the one that shows more sides of myself
For example, there's a cool, nice-looking side of me here
There's also the side of me where it's like I'm in a party
In the jacket photo, it consists of private, off-shots, things like that
I want to show various sides of myself
So this is also nice, but we decided to use it for the artist photo
This is the jacket photo
There are many things here
It's full of pictures I didn't upload to Instagram or Twitter
Also, there were people who asked me "what is this?!"
This is actually Pocky. The reason I wanted to use this was
When I did a SHOWROOM on Pocky Day
I wanted to have Pocky but didn't have any so I made some myself
I made something like cookie dough with chocolate
That's why, when people look at it
those who watched the SHOWROOM stream that day will go
"Ah, this was the Pocky from that day"
I tried to put in some small details like that
Anyway, the lyrics of the songs from 1 to 9 were all written by myself
It's playing in the background at the moment
I haven't really talked much about these songs
I even had to take a hiatus, really sorry about that.
I'd like to talk about these songs today
The staff politely prepared all these panels for me
They made flip cards for me
So I'm going to introduce the songs
The first song is "Sofa to Cushion"
This song is pretty straightforward
I likened a man to a sofa, and a woman to a cushion
It's a couple's song
When we say "Sofa and Cushion"
They're definitely a set, aren't they?
So the guy and the girl are one set
We'll always be together, we'll never be apart
Let our relationship be like a sofa and a cushion
That kind of lyrics
Talking about the lyrics is kind of embarrassing
The lyrics that I wrote myself
Somehow, to explain it all like that
It's kind of embarrassing
But the meaning of the lyrics
Can completely change depending on who's listening to it
So I'm not saying this is the definitely the correct interpretation of the lyrics
I'll be happy if all of you could listen to it while thinking of
your own partners or people in your life
Ah, someone commented "I like this song".
Thank you
Toshi-san is at #1 right now
Amazing! Thank you very much.
What's this? The round human-like thing?
Somehow Juripanda-san and Aoi-san are also round humans
I don't know.
When I do a stream, there's usually a lot of choco-neko avatars
Because I said I liked choco-neko
Okay, moving on
The second song, "Monochrome"
This is a song from a man's perspective
What initially inspired me to write this was
I also want guys to sing in Karaoke for me
It's a song that I want guys to sing for the girl they like
Furthermore, "I want to protect you", "I want to hold you"
"Just by looking at you, my head is full of your smiling face"
These are words I want a guy to say to me
The words that I want said to me, I put them in lyrics
I started with writing the chorus
Then when I was trying to decide how I want
the A and B melodies to be
I imagined a guy who hasn't had much experience with love
Someone who's lived like that
Living in a world without colour, with nobody around him
Living through really boring days
But he met someone he likes
colourful days start to come to him
It's a song about that
This song is pretty popular I think, "Monochrome"
I guess everyone has someone that they like, maybe
"It's a song you wrote for me" is in the comments LOL
That's funny
"It made me cry", really?!
"It's a lovely setting", thank you very much
Someone wrote "chou suki"
Moving on...
"Anata no te"
This is a song about being separated from
people who were important in the past
So in this song the narrator understands they've broken up
But even so, because of that person, the narrator was able to overcome tough times
It's a song like that
But this is the saddest song, isn't it?
Somehow, breaking up
"I thought I understood that the day we separate will come but"
"So why am I remembering the warmth of your hands, even now even now?"
This is, a man- for example you can think of it as the feelings of a woman in love with a man
Or the feelings of a man in love with a woman
It's not just about romantic love, but also when you've lost something important
It's a song about these feelings
That's why among the 9 songs
I think this is the saddest one
But because that person was there,
or because that thing was there
I was saved... It's kind of bright but kind of sad too
"Wow, they're all pretty deep" was in the comments
"It's my favourite". "It makes me cry"
"TT"
"It's the next step"
"It's so sad", "I like the melody too" Thank you
I'm happy
Moving on, "Aishiteru"
This one,
It's a song about a super troublesome woman
But I'm actually this type of person
If you look at the chorus you'll know
" 'I love you', I want you to say it to me now"
" 'I love you', Look into my eyes when you say it"
"Don't say you 'like me', say you 'love me'"
"Not even 'I really like you' but 'I love you'"
That's what I wrote
Anyway, saying "suki" is enough isn't it? "Daisuki" is also okay
You might be thinking that but
But being told "Aishiteru yo" makes me the happiest
New Japan Pro-Wrestling- btw I like pro-wrestling
NJPW's Tanahashi-senshu, whenever he wraps up in his MC performance
He would end with "Everyone in the arena, Aishitemasu!"
I think that's really great
Ah, "Ai" can be said to family too
You can say that to a person you like too
You can say that to members, and also to fans
That's why, how do I say this
"Suki" or "daisuki" are things you end up saying lightly
Because the word "Aishiteru" carries some weight
So that's something, how do I say this
It's a girl who's begging for someone to say that to her
So it's a song about heart pounding moments and
living happily and loving everyday and
"It's possible to enjoy everything like this", type of contents
That's why everyone please tell me "Aishiteru"
Everyone flood the comments feed with "Aishiteru" now~
Comment pleaseu~
I wonder if that worked
Ah, "Aishitemasu", "Aishiteru"...
I'm going to drink the pudding milk tea I bought earlier
Just a bit of a break
Wow, lots of "aishiteru" there. "Aishiteru aishiteru"...
Of course "Aishiteru" is great isn't it?
Yaa... Amazing! "Aishiteru"
"Aishiteraburu" - That's an SKE song
Aishiteraburu~!
Amazing, there are English comments saying "I love you". There are Korean comments saying "Sarang haeyo" too.
I'm happy~ Thank you
Ah! Eh?
Is it tapioca? That guy
The round person is a tapioca? I love tapioca!
I didn't know that. Because I haven't been doing this recently.
Ah!
I got something from Yurimana-san...
I received an octopus! Thank you so much!
I'm waiting for items too~
Okay, moving on...
It's coming it's coming, kamatte dance
KMT Dance
So for this one, I kind of made a buzz with it on TikTok
This is another troublesome one!
A troublesome woman's song
I'm really a kamatte-chan
Even though I look like this and might be thought of as strong
I have a personality where I cannot survive without being pampered by others
But I can't do that to my family, so I always do it to members
Anyway the inspiration for this song was
When I was talking on LINE with someone,
That person sent me a "Kamatte Dance" stamp
Seeing that I thought, "Kamatte Dance? That's pretty interesting"
"Okay, let's make it into a song"
So I tried writing the song
Um, what was I going to say
Oh yes, another thing.
There was another reason I wanted to write this song
Akimoto-sensei's lyrics are
his hit songs, a lot of them usually have repeated phrases
For example "Aitakatta" is kind of an earworm isn't it?
[sings Aitakatta]
It gets stuck in your head
Anyway, when I wanted to make a song like "Aitakatta" where
you get addicted to it as you listen to it more
"Kamatte, kamatte, kamatte" was what I went with
These are kind of corner-cutting lyrics isn't it?
Actually the first and second parts in the lyrics are all the same
I deliberately made them match.
The second part's A melody?
"Sukoshi kurai kocchi ni mite yo"
this is also the same with this other part
"Watashi konna ni matteiru no yo"
"Sukoshi kurai kocchi ni mite yo"
"Watashi konna ni omotteru no yo"
It's all the same
This is kind of creepy at the end here isn't it?
"Kamatte kamatte kamatte kamatte kamatte..."
So I ended up writing a pretty silly song
But it's good that it's easy to remember
Oh right! At a handshake event, the children who came also
Did "Kamatte dance" together with me
So there's a dance for this song. Let's do it once
T-t-television is not right.
Those of you in front of your screens can do it too
1, 2
KAMATTE DANCE
Good job! Everyone can do this one
Even the kids who come to the handshake event could do it
Moving on, "Stay with me"
Ah this one, too.
I took all the words I want a man to say and put them in the lyrics
"Your innocent laughing face, your angry and sulking face"
"All of them I love and they drive me crazy"
"You fluster me to the point where I don't know what to do"
Also the 2nd verse
"Your tired and sleepy face, your face that wants to be pampered"
"All of them I love and they drive me crazy"
"You fluster me to the point where I don't know what to do"
I do want to fluster a guy!
I wonder if it was alright to say that
People at my agency might be in a commotion about it
But really even at handshake events, how do I say this
I'm usually the one who's flustered
My fans would tell me things like, "I love you"
They tell me things like that
When that happens, I want to fluster other people too
So that's why, using my own cuteness
I want to make a guy flustered
Things like that, so I'm currently researching love
Even with lyric-writing
You can't really do it without experiencing various things
The truth is I've always wanted to be a lyricist
I really like Akimoto-sensei's lyrics
That's why I really enjoy interpreting the meanings of the lyrics
When I read them, I always felt like writing my own lyrics
In order to keep writing lyrics,
I want to experience various things
Even liking a person is something I think I want to do more
Furthermore, this is where I challenged myself to rap for the first time
The lyrics for the rap are also in there
That's also one part I worked hard for so I hope you'll listen to it too
I wonder what people are commenting on
"I want to go to your handshake event, please come to Hokkaido!"
I really want to go to Hokkaido! I even just had Hokkaido ramen.
This is totally irrelevant but
At Shibuya I had Hokkaido ramen and bought this drink, before coming here
"Kakkoii" is in the comments
"The rap was good" -- thank you
"You look well"
"What about being Akimoto-sensei's apprentice?"
Oh yes, after I graduate I do want to learn from Akimoto-sensei
Hold on, my bangs are in the way
After I graduate, I want to be attached to Akimoto-sensei to learn various things
I really do think about doing that
But I'm not going to do it just yet
I'm just thinking about my future there
Moving on...
This is the weirdest song
Hm, is "weird" the right word...
It starts off with a gong sound
I like pro-wrestling, so I tried having it start off with the gong
But actually, originally the gong sound wasn't in there
In the chorus, "Maji tsumaranee, maji kudaranee"
"Sonna hibi wa good bye (good night)"
Kenny Omega who used to be in NJPW, but is now in an organisation called AEW
I decided to use his signature phrase in the song
Also in the 2nd verse, "Sou omattamon kachisa (champion)" is in there too
And even in the intro, there was a shout of "IYAO!" in there
That was originally NJPW's Nakamura Shinsuke's...
He's currently a wrestler in WWE
It's his signature phrase and I decided to put it in
I made this with a pro-wrestling feel
The time I started thinking about writing this song was
when I was in Majisuka Gakuen
It was AKB's TV drama series
I wrote this song during that time
That's why I put the word "maji" in there
I tried putting in "maji tsumaranee, maji kudaranee"
It's like a delinquent... it's a delinquent song.
"I'm not interested in being a normal, good and serious kid"
"It's fine to cut loose sometimes"
"Parents and respected teachers"
"Don't get pushed by them"
"Your own path, you decide for yourself"
It's a delinquent, but it's a mild delinquent
It's not someone who's only bad
It's someone who's telling you not to waste even one moment in life
It's someone who's unexpectedly conveying a strong message
I really like this one
I can also joke around with it
I also did call-and-response with fans
This part, "YOLO YOLO Yoroshiku ne!"
And fans will respond, "YOLO YOLO Yoroshiku ne!"
"Y. O. L. O. Yoroshiku ne!"
YO! YO! LO! LO!
"Jinsei tatta ichido kiri YAY!"
I definitely want to do it in a concert, so I hope you all remember it
Yes, that's right!
Oh wow everyone's typing it out, thanks so much
Just a little bit more till we hit 10000
I wonder if that will happen
I want it to hit 10000
In my past streams I think it was normal to hit 30000
Okay let's move on
There's two left
Hold on, my stamina... my stamina is at its limit
My bulging stomach is about to be exposed
"Only those who want to come along should come!"
"Only those who want to watch the stream should watch it!"
Okay moving on, this is a popular one
This is an idol song, "Chu yori kiss"
This one, well it's actually my feelings too
It's mostly...
Well it's not my first-hand experience but...
Sorry, my finger is injured
It's not my first-hand experience, but I imagined words that I want said to me
"Said to me"? Probably "done to me"
I think I've mostly been treated like a kid
Or maybe an adult? When I'm in this industry
I'm sometimes treated like an adult, but also treated like a kid
I entered when I was 11, even after 11 years I'm 22
"22 years old, you're still a kid", I'm told things like that
I really hated that
So I wanted to write lyrics that say "Don't treat me like a kid!"
But if it's only that, it's kinda boring
So I thought it'd be cute to say it in a cute way, so it became this idol song
So I acted the part of a selfish girl
who has friends around her...
They're adult-like, and go on dates with their boyfriends
And go on drive dates
"I want to do those things soon too"
That kind of feel
"Don't treat me like a kid, treat me like an adult"
It's that kind of song
So about "Chu yori kiss"
"Chu" is kind of cute isn't it? But "kiss" sounds like it has a sexy feel
That's why, "don't do the child-like Chu, but do the adult-like Kiss"
So it's a song like that
"Your eyebrows are fat" is written there
Are my eyebrows fat??
I don't really do anything for my eyebrows, I usually leave it as is
I thought it was just right
You're all focused on something totally irrelevant
"They're not fat, they're not fat" -- That's right!
It isn't fat right? "They're not fat", "That's not true", there are comments like that
They're not fat, right?
Eh? I wonder if it's alright?
The only part that's fat is probably my tummy
It's fine like this isn't it?
Don't say "don't make me laugh"
They're not fat, my eyebrows are definitely not fat. You're mean!
"It might be the balance with your eyes" -- Who made my eyes like this??!
Natural! Natural! Natural faceu~!
Okay moving on, this is the last one
This is also popular I think
This is the only one where I wrote about my feelings towards my SKE life over 11 years
I sang this a lot before the Sousenkyo
It's a song that I did when I think of my fans
The inspiration for this song was
There was a friend who's from Nagoya
From Nagoya? From Aichi-ken. It's a friend who's in the entertainment industry
I made a promise with that friend
to become an actress or actor
and to walk the red carpet together
"Let's become actors" or "let's become an actress", we made a promise like that
It's really difficult on the way to reaching that dream and keeping that promise
But "it's alright if we're both working hard", that kind of hometown love?
So that happened
So as I was writing the lyrics, I thought
"This works for conveying my feelings to my fans too"
In the lead up to the SSK it was really difficult and I was under immense pressure
Especially since it was the 10th SSK, and it was even in Nagoya
Everytime I go on a TV show people would tell me "You're definitely going to be No.1"
"You'll definitely become no.1" things like that were said to me
I was really feeling crushed under the pressure
Lots of things happened, and I felt really sorry for that time
My sense of responsibility might have been too strong
but because there are fans who support me no matter what
I was able to not give up and kept working hard
So over here, I'm keeping my promise to be no.1 in SSK, and I haven't forgotten that promise
Originally, it was a promise I made with that friend to be active together and
in an assertive way, to become Nagoya and Aichi's star, or become a world star
It was that kind of song
But you can interpret it in many different ways
It's a song I want people to listen to if they have hopes and dreams and want to work hard towards realising their dreams
If you look around you, even if you didn't notice, you may have many allies cheering you on
I'm actually fighting with my family right now
Honestly there are times where I felt I wanted to move out of the house
And now I also feel like moving out because of this but
But I'm grateful to my family who raised me up
So I have to reconcile with my family after all
That's something I realised when I listened to this song, I will try to reconcile today
OH! It's happening!
The audience! The audience? The viewer rating? The audience?
My stupidity is getting exposed
We've just hit 10000!!! Thank you so much!
"Why did you fight" was written there
Well, really... how do I say this
Honestly, it's an accumulation of stress
Humans are like that aren't they?
When you're under a lot of stress, you’ll want to release it somewhere
And really, that's often your family members
During those times, I'll be asked "why are you taking it out on me?"
"It's because you're family" -- something like that
Up until now, I didn't have a rebellious phase
Having started at 11, I was way too busy
And my mother is someone I really love
Because my mother really worked hard for me by herself
And she raised me up
I only have feelings of gratitude for my mother
And actually helping my mother was one of the reasons that I entered this industry
That's why I didn't have a rebellious phase but
But somehow recently, I'm having a rebellious phase
I'm not really sure about it but
That's also a good experience
It's something I can use for lyrics
That experience will be helpful for being an actress
Thinking of that, I need to reconcile properly
Because I still have some childish aspects
That's right
Hm, what's that?
"It's better to have a rebellious phase",  "that's really late!"
Yes, I am having a late rebellious phase
But my mother is important to me, why is this happening so late
Being pampered by my mother has become kind of embarrassing, I think
That's why
I'm in a rebellious phase
Reconciling, yes I will reconcile
Even today, I properly sent her a text saying "Please watch the stream today~"
I'm sure it'll be fine
She's really kind
About parents, they don't really let you become independent
Children will want to be independent at some point but
But a parent will think that they'll always be the parent
But from my perspective, I'm no longer a child
It's true that I'll always be her daughter but
I was never going to be a child forever
That's difficult
So that's what I'm worrying a bit about but
That's something I can put in lyrics
And it'd be great if I could release a CD or something
I'd like to be able to sing to many kinds of people through my lyrics
Do we still have time?
What should I talk about?
Since I'm here, I might as well read comments from the fans
Maybe I'll answer some questions
If you have any questions please send them through
Hm!
"Do the Kamatte Dance to your mother"
Mm..?
What's that? It's too fast...
"That beverage you're drinking, is it not tapioca?"
Nope! This one has pudding in it.
I like tapioca too though.
It's got pudding in it. I bought it in Shibuya around Center-gai
I just walked normally around Center-Gai, it was fun
"If there's a SSK again will you participate?"
Yaa, that's a really difficult question!
Last year, I was able to win no.1 due to everyone's help
But my body broke down
I wasn't able to do any activities as #1
So yeh I'd like to participate and be #1 again
This time I want to be the center
I do want to become AKB's center
SKE's center is now Suda-chan but
What I'm aiming for is...
Well, being SKE's center is also important but
Really I want to become AKB or 48g's center
That's what I think
Because Yahagi-chan also quit although she just became center, that's really sad
And Minegishi-san also just announced her graduation
AKB's 1st gen are all no longer around
That's really lonely
In addition to loneliness, I think as as the new AKB and 48g
We need to keep it going
That's what's on my mind right now
If I can be even a little bit of help
I think I'd definitely want to be the center
Of course I know there is much criticism about me
For me it's really 50-50
There are really passionate fans
There are also people really attacking me
So it's 50-50
But I think I get really high viewership ratings
Even today, maybe
It's probably not half but
Today around 80% are my fans
The remaining 20% are probably kind of anti-like people, I think
But the fact that they're even watching makes me grateful
So thank you very much for that, that's what I think
"You should try doing kennin again"
About that, kennin, I'm not even sure I can do that
But if it's now, I think I can enjoy it
In the past I was too passionate
I felt like I had to, how do I say this
Keep up with all the older sisters, and that exhausted me
Right now I'm able to think that I need to enjoy myself while doing it
So that makes me hap.. Mm, what's the right word, happy?
But actually even without kennin, we can enter AKB's senbatsu
That's something I'm really grateful for
But obviously that's not something that's a certainty
SKE is the same
Because this group has a selection system
Even with so many members
Only a handful of members can enter senbatsu
This time I was dropped from SKE's senbatsu
I was given a solo song but
This time I experienced being dropped from senbatsu
As I expected, how do I say this
Rather than being disappointed
Sad? Well that's not right either
But anyway, with my absence other members would be able to enter
And Suda-chan was able to become center
Other members also get their turn to shine
That's something that makes me happy too
I'm taking it positively like that
Up until now, had this happened I probably would've gone "KIII~ WHY??!"
Now, I'm not really worried about it, and I can actually loosen up
I think maybe I've become an adult
But with my family, I'm still a kid going through a rebellious phase
Next, next
Is it about time now?
Alright, so it's time
"Yosusu isn't here yet?" Hahaha
Yoshimasa-san is not going to come!
This time, for my solo album I wrote all the lyrics but
The composer is Yoshimasa-san, Inoue Yoshimasa-san who composed all the songs
It's a lovely piece of work, recording was also fun
Alright! Let's wrap up there and move to the announcements segment
I'd like to make some announcements here
That's okay right? I'll do the announcements now
Alright, so...
To commemorate the release of the album,
Here on SHOWROOM, we will be broadcasting
a premium live concert! Yay!!
I think this was announced the last time too
But I ended up going on hiatus
So, this is a postponed concert
If I show this we'll end up showing both announcements, I'll show it later
For this, the title will be
Maybe I'll just cover it like this
The title has been decided
For the first date, 6 January 2020 at 8pm there will be a broadcast for the premium concert
The title will be, "Matsui Jurina's First Solo Concert ~Without Audience, I Will Sing For You~"
So what this is about is
Although I did 11 years with SKE and AKB,
I've actually never done a solo concert
But this time I'll be doing it through a broadcast without an audience
So it's like I'm basically singing only for you
If you want to know what it's like, it's going to be like a music show on TV
It'll be like a fancam
I'm the only one being shown, that kind of concert
It will feel like I'm singing only for you
"First CD, first CD"
This will be on SHOWROOM by the way
That's right. First solo concert on SHOWROOM.
It will be on my account, definitely watch it
Also, moving on...
Finally, there's a campaign that was announced and planned
It's an opportunity to watch the live rehearsal
We will be having an additional lottery to choose additional winners! Yatta!
So this is the one, 6 Jan 2020 premium concert's live rehearsal participants will be increased
So for this one, we've already contacted the 15 people who were chosen
An additional 23 people will also be invited
Why 23 people?
My birthday is on 8 March, on the 3rd month, 8th day, so that's 38!
So that's why we're planning to invite 38 people to the live rehearsal observation
So there's that
But please be reassured
Regarding the lottery, those who have already made a purchase are eligible to participate
So please rest assured
Also, those who want to win this should buy more of the albums
So about this audienceless concert
Those who can come and watch the live rehearsal will mostly be fine
Eh? Yoshimasa-san came to watch the stream?
Where?
"By Inoue Yoshimasa" is written there
Ah! Yoshimasa-san is here!
Yoshimasa-san, thank you so much! Yoshimasa-san is at number 5
Thank you so much, for making so many great songs for me
My first solo concert will be broadcast on 6 Jan!
Yoshimasa-san is seriously
When I tell him "I want this kind of song"
He's always able to compose exactly that kind of song, and I'm super happy about that
But Yoshimasa-san said his strongest impression was
The difference between Akimoto-sensei and Jurina is that I write the lyrics first
Akimoto-sensei seems like he actually chooses the song first, then writes the lyrics
But in my case, I write the lyrics thinking "this should be the A-melody", "this is the B-melody"
"This is the chorus", things like that
So I actually think of the song in my head before writing it out
Yoshimasa-san says it makes it really easy to compose for
He commented "笑笑笑笑” (laughing)
He commented "it was easy to compose for"
I was really happy to receive such great songs, thank you so much
Anyway, let's return to the topic at hand
Those who are coming to the live rehearsal
They're probably people who haven't done that before
The thing I'm secretly thinking of right now is
I might perform certain songs only at the live rehearsal
So there are songs like that, that I want to perform
If you manage to get drawn in the lottery, that would be great
Actually I really want everyone to get drawn though
Anyway this is my first attempt at a solo concert
Without any audience, I sing only to you
I think this is probably a first for any 48g member
To perform a solo concert without an audience, it's a first
It's similar to a SHOWROOM isn't it?
It's a concert that is done in order to do a SHOWROOM stream
Also, another thing
There's a certain famous band that did an audienceless concert
[She's talking about X-Japan]
And it become quite a hot topic didn't it?
I'm not doing an audienceless concert because of that
It's because of various things that we just happened to be doing a concert without audience
But of course if it also becomes a hot topic that'd be great
Everyone, I'll be happy if you could liven this up for me
"Maesetsu wa Maeda-shachou" is written there AHAHAHA
That's so funny
Maeda-shachou... He's the SHOWROOM (CEO)
"Ukeru", "Tanoshimi tanoshimi", "I love you~"
"Will Yoshimasa-san be in charge of MC?" -- Yoshimasa-san is not going to come that day
Yoshimasa-san isn't going to be there
If Yoshimasa-san comes, he'll be taking over everything won't he?
"I'm looking forward to it", "will your rehearsal be in Kanto?"
It will be Kanto, right? I can say this right?
I will be doing it in Kanto, so those who are drawn will have to come to a place in Kanto
If you can come to the live house I'd be happy
I'll be doing some livestreamed concerts after this too
Well not just livestreamed concerts, but normal concerts too
You might be wondering "What's Jurina's concerts like?"
Or you might be wondering what I'm like solo
I want more people to see it but
We're going to start with a livestreamed concert this time.
I'd be happy if you enjoy it
Maybe...
According to my schedule, I'll be in Tokyo that day
I'll only be able to do this in Tokyo
If someone from Nagoya or other regions get drawn in the lottery
They'll need to come to Tokyo for the rehearsal
I feel bad about that but
I hope you'll try to come anyway
Alright, so I think we'll quickly wrap up
It's already near the ending now
In no time at all...
Oh if I do this my bulging stomach will be discovered
I've really gained a lot of weight
Can someone please tell me some ways to lose weight?
Could you all post some comments on ways to lose weight?
"You're cute", it's moving really fast... "Sarang haeyo"
"Do a performance" -- Yes, that's right
Maybe dancing will help
"Going to the gym would be good"
I want to do some muscle training, but I'm not sure I have the body for that
My body is all worn-out
I actually went to a chiropractor
And they told me "Jurina-san, your body is 90 years old"
I went "90 years old?!"
90-years old... "But today it's 50-years old" was what they told me
That's kind of bad too, I'm still only 22
It's because I've been overdoing it for 10 years
I didn't really take care of my body
At the moment there are people who are helping to care for my body
Right now I do have a well-prepared system for care
In the beginning, everything I ate was deep fried in bento boxes
Right now I'm really blessed
I think there are some kids who don't realise or know how lucky they are when they're young
So sometimes I try to mention, "this is good, in the beginning we didn't have such warm bento boxes to eat"
"I'm really happy now, thank you so much"
But really when I was younger I really overdid it too much
My body is all worn out
But I still want to go all out with dancing
That's why I'm receiving a lot of care so that I can deliver a great performance to everyone
It's going to be on 6 January, okay? 6 January
I hope I'll pull it together and do it well
But, on 6 January, I want to say this, but I wonder if I should be saying this now
Regarding what kind of style the concert will be
I really want to say this but I think I'll leave it as a surprise for everyone to look forward to
But before that, there will be a talk-time during the concert
There will be various things planned before we start the performances
It will be structured that way
Everyone, it starts at 8pm
It will be for around an hour I think, the concert
I hope you all come to see it
I will be singing only for you who is behind the screen
You'll come see it, right?
"I hope you'll make some merchandise too" -- Oh yes,
I think there will be things like that too
"I have an hour to spare" was commented there
"Thanks, I'll watch it~ can I comment on the stream?"
Comments are allowed right?
Yes, during the livestream comments will be enabled
So please do so
I'd also like to point out the comments myself
Maybe I'll make some time for that kind of thing
"How do I apply to join?" there are comments about that here
But for more details please check out the homepage
We'll upload the details there, so please check it there
What's going on here?
"Daisuki daisuki"
"We can watch it while waving penlights" -- Yes that sounds good!
That's great actually
We could make the venue a little darker
Then if I see penlights waving on the screen
It might feel like a real concert
"I love you" came in the comments
Thanks to you overseas viewers too
Toshi-san you've been in #1 all along! Amazing!
The goods too- not goods, I mean there are lots of items too
Wow! Lilia-san you threw 5000 hearts
That's amazing. Thanks so much
"It feels like a live viewing doesn't it?" -- Yes that's right
It'd be great if you could watch it
You can watch it nationwide, right?
With SHOWROOM, you could even watch it from overseas
So since it's nationwide, it's amazing isn't it?
That means this is kind of like a nationwide solo concert
It's an event where lots of people can come to see
Thank you so much, I'm happy
"How many cameras will you have?" -- That's what you're interested in?!
You're really interested in that, aren't you?
Yaaa~
What's this, it's an international broadcast
It's really... great
"Because of all these, it's better for you to lose weight" -- Oi!
I already know that!
I know that, but my tummy is bouncy! What am I supposed to do?
And I even had ramen earlier...
Whenever I go on a hiatus I'd gain weight!
That's why next time I definitely won't go on hiatus
There definitely won't be a 3rd time, I think
Mmm?
"Do you intend to do a head-on challenge with X-Japan?"
X! X!
I like it. I like bands actually.
The other day I went to a live concert by an artist from the same company as SKE, our company Zest
They're a band called BRIDEAR, I went to watch them perform
The performance was super exciting
Yes, let's do maintenance for the body
"Make sure you keep warm" -- I will keep warm
Ah, it looks like time's up
Let's finish with...
One time of...
Right, Kamatte Dance is now playing, so let's all do it once
1, 2!
KAMATTE DANCE
This part makes me really want to dance
WHOO!
I'm getting carried away
Doesn't feel like the ending at all
Isn't this the opening?
Anyway, there are still lots of things I wanted to say but
Thanks everyone for watching till the end!
Alright! I'll do this
Let's summarise
6 Jan 2020 at 8pm will be the premium live concert
Matsui Jurina's First Solo Concert ~Without Audience, I Will Sing For You~"
Also, regarding the live rehearsal observation for the premium live concert an additional draw has also been prepared
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
Regarding the method to apply for this
There will be a banner, this one over here
Please check it out over here
Details will be uploaded there
Please submit your application there
Was there still one thing I still have to say?
Ah, right!
The broadcast will be in this room
To the top right of your screen, there will be a heart mark
If you register this as your favourite
When the broadcast starts you will get a notification so you won't forget
And you'll be able to watch, so definitely do that
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu
Alright, that's a wrap. This was Matsui Jurina.
May all of you have great days ahead of you
It's a bit early for Christmas but
Please also have fun for Christmas
I hope that each one of your days will be great!
Thank you so much!
All of you are sofas! Bye bye!
I'm the cushion~!