Everyone, good evening!
I'm Matsui Jurina, who just made a graduation announcement
How's everyone feeling, I wonder?
Are you sad?
Because it's a positive announcement
How do I say this, you might be cheering me on instead
I wonder which one it is
So this just came on
This is from the album that was on sale
The song from the album just came on
A song called "Anata no te" I wrote thinking about farewells
It's a really sad so-
Eh?! There's already 15 thousand viewers? You're kidding!
Wow! Thanks so much!
Thanks for being so interested in this
So this is my first SHOWROOM since the recent live event commemorating my first solo album
Anyway, without further ado
I have some announcements to make
The schedule of my graduation concert has been decided
It will be on 26 and 27 September
The venue will be Nihon Gaishi Hall
Yay!
So I'll be doing the graduation concert in September and
The schedule for my graduation theatre performance has also been decided
My graduation theatre performance will be on 5 October, our 12th anniversary!
Yay!
So about the 12th anniversary, how do I say this
It wouldn't have been right to announce this at such an important event for SKE
But as the final 1st generation member, I would like to finish my 12 years properly
Also, with only the two of us-
Not the "two of us", just me lol.
Who's here with me, that's scary lol
For today, it would be lonely to do this on my own so
So I called comrades from the same generation
Satou Mieko-chan, and also Nakanishi Yuuka-chan, please come in!
Eh? I'm so happy!
- Well done on your graduation announcement!
- Thank you! I'm happy! The flowers have come!
Thank you
It's Mama and Papa
I'm getting married! This is Mama and Papa!
- You can make it Mama and Mama
- The both of you are married now aren't you?
- Yes, that's right
- You're both other people's wives
- You're being sandwiched by wives
- I'm becoming Othello!
- We're the wives and Othello
There's a weird energy here right now
Wanna put the flowers here?
Ah yes, thanks. I'm happy
Ah, the comments are coming in
"It's been a while since we saw Papa"
- They're making fun of you, saying you're handsome
- They're calling Mieko the Papa
There's no way that's true LOL
But actually back in spring I hung out with Nakanishi
At that time she was more feminine
But just for today, she returned to her previous form
Truly a professional!!
I didn't return!
Since we met today we've had this exchange about 10 times
- Because it was shocking to me!
- You didn't really change
Only Jurina says that to me
No, I meant you didn't change from way back
Oh you meant since 5 years ago? Thank you
- They're saying you're an ikemen
- They're praising you!
Mieko, there might be people who don't know us
Please introduce yourself!
Uh, over here? Here? Here?
That was cute
I'm a graduated 1st gen SKE member, Satou Mieko! Yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
Neesan!
Neesan! Neesan!
I'm the same, Nakanishi Yuuka
Was it this one?
I'm the same, Nakanishi Yuuka! Yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
- "We know you", was written there
- Thank you!
- Ah, thank you!
- You were beautiful today!
Really today, how do I say this
It felt like I was seeing Matsui Jurina for the first time in a while
- Am I not always Matsui Jurina?
- No, what I mean is
Recently we go out for meals often don't we?
- In your private time you mean?
- That's right!
It was amazing, seriously
Like an idol?
No, rather than an idol...
"Star"
Star! Nice pronunciation
- But seriously it was great
- Eh, for the both of you, where were your graduation conc-
Concerts? I mean where did you two graduate?
- T... theatre...?
- It was the theatre?
Somehow Gaishi has a strong impression on me
Gaishi? That wasn't us at all LOL
That was someone else
At Gaishi, important members, how do I say this...
I have a really strong image of Gaishi as a place where our douki graduated
Yeah, I think I was there a lot
We were there together on the national tour
Masana graduated there too
Sae-chan also graduated there
I went to see that one
Oh really?
That's why, for me to be doing it at Gaishi
It really gives me deep feelings
- It's a memorable place
- Yes, it's a memorable place
- I understand
- I'm so happy
I'd wanted to go to Nagoya Dome one more time
But
The truth is I also wanted to graduate at a memorable place
So to be able to do it in Gaishi, I'm quite happy
The first time we performed at Gaishi was also memorable
Yesterday, I had a meal with Jurina
And we'd already talked about the ideal graduation concert
We decided on half of the setlist arbitrarily
- You've already decided on it?
- Arbitrarily
I can't reveal the setlist but
There's something I want to do no matter what
So there's SKE's previous theatre manager, Yuasa-san
Around the time of the 10th anniversary performance
There were plans to assemble all the 1st generations to do a reunion performance
It wasn't "we wanted to do it", but "we're doing it"
So that was announced, but
At the end it wasn't realised
- He went somewhere far away
- So because of that, the graduated 1st gens were asked by fans
"Aren't you going to do it?"
It caused a lot of trouble for them
I think I heard about this
So that's what I heard
And honestly I was really looking forward to it myself
- Ah there are comments saying Yuasa-san has tweeted
Because Yuasa-san tends to talk a lot
I didn't tell him about the announcement
So he's going to go like "Ehhh?"
- So I actually rang him up to apologise earlier
- So that's who you were talking to before this
- That's why, I want to make this a reality
- Because I'm the only 1st gen left
- After Jurina graduates nobody else is left to do this
- The last of the 1st gen
- That's right, because there's nobody else
At Gaishi, there won't be only one performance
It's going to be for two days
So on either one of those days
I'd like for the 1st gens to assemble
And do a concert together
That's your ambition
That's right, it's my ambition
So, it's not just a reunion stage
I want to do a reunion concert
So I have ambitions to make that happen
If I offer it to the both of you, will you come?
- I'll go
- Well, yes I want to go
- Really?
- Yes I want to go
You'll wear the costumes?
You'll wear the Party* costume?
[*Party ga hajimaru yo]
Hold on, only I'm wearing Party?
Jurina's wearing something like this, and I'm wearing Party?
- Nakanishi should wear Party shouldn't she?
- Why?
- The pink checkered one?
- Yep!
- Only me?
- "Aozora no soba ni ite" is okay too
- The strange and short one
Am I stuck with the Party stage?
Only Nakanishi
Then I think I'll do "Kisu dame"
[Kiss wa dame yo]
The one with the bigass round beads
Those who don't know it, please google it
- Sorry about that our...
- I'd like you all to search for it
- The pictures of Nakanishi from that time
- Stop it! Stop it!
- Please find it
- "Are you doing a punishment game?"
- Yes, if it's only me...
- Oh there's already 20 thousand!
- 20 thousand!
- Among the 20 thousand, someone will find that costume
- 20k in 10 mins, has that ever happened?
- Amazing!
- Thank you!
- Thank you
They're really surprised I think
We knew about it before this
So that's why we're like "Yay!!"
But the fans are probably kind of depressed
Also on Twitter
We're asking for messages with the hashtag Arigatou Jurina
ABUNAI!!! SAFEU~!!!
It was fine
Is it alright to be this cheery after a grad announcement
The people watching this might still be in shock
The lockscreen is on I think
I know the password
Ah, that wasn't the right password
That's the wrong password
Ah thanks to those who sent gifts
"You're all really excited" is written there
"It's like the old Team S MC"
- Weren't you nervous before you went on?
- I was super nervous
- So it's like you broke free
I'm trying to get the #ArigatouJurina hashtag feed
How is it otousan?
- Otousan?
- It's like an otousan reading the papers
- Are you alright? Have you used it before?
- (male voice) Uhh... Where should I press?
There are a lot of good comments
- Thanks for the comments
- I wonder which one I should read
- "I'm happy to see you cheerful as usual" is written
- Jurina with a smile is the best is what people want to see the most isn't it?
- Moreover, it's honestly a bit different when Jurina is with only 1st gens isn't it?
- There's a sense of success isn't there?
- A sense of success
- You've been with me since I was a 6th grader
- You're all grown up~
- You're 22 now
[They're saying 22 years old in a cute way]
- I've decided
- Which one?
"I was really happy that I came to like Jurina"
"Of course, after this I'll continue to like you"
"But the idol Jurina was too important to me"
"So I'm crying right now, but I'll support you with all I have"
"Congratulations on your graduation announcement. Love you!"
- Eh, I'm happy. You read a good comment
- I really understand the feeling of fans
As an idol fan
- "For me, Jurina was my life"
- Eh? That's amazing
- Maybe we'll read the messages with this hashtag with Jurina later
- I wonder if there are any questions?
- Right, some questions are good too
The comments from here are fine too
The SHOWROOM comments
So Jurina, how are you feeling right now? Relieved?
Hmm, I thought it'd be harder to announce it
Even last night, in my head
I was imagining doing the graduation announcement in my head
At that time I went, "I can't do this!"
"I can't say it!!"
Before the start I was like "I can't say it! I can't say it!" while wearing my shoes
Regardless, I sang the song
Then everyone came out
Then I talked about the current state of SKE
Because of everyone's growth, I was able to take step outwards
That's what I really thought
So I was able to just say it
- Also you probably got some power from looking at the faces of fans
- Yes that's right
- Like a switch flipped
- But really when you were singing you looked brilliant, I thought it was amazing
At first we thought you would announce before singing
So we were all worked up for nothing
- Eh? Is that so?
- I thought, "the members are going to surround you now?"
"Are they about to? Dokidokidoki... Oh it's the song first"
Because we knew in advance
That's why I listened thinking Jurina might cry
It was amazing
Yesterday Neesan told me, "don't cry at the announcement"
Like, "do the concert properly"
When I heard that I thought "yes, that's true"
Even if I were to bawl out there
It's a positive graduation
It wouldn't be good, was what I thought
So I decided to do it properly
- Because yesterday she said about 3 times "I'm gonna cry!"
- I did cry twice
- You did, during the meal
- I called a staff member who helped me a lot
And mentioned I would announce it tomorrow
The staff member said "well done for all these years"
And I went "thank you so much~" while crying
- It's too early for that
- The graduation is in October so we might be able to stream a lot
- Yeah, and these days mobile phones are so convenient
The questions are coming in
- Oh, about your post-graduation plans, what will you do?
- Yes, what will you be doing?
- I think that's what everyone wants to know the most
- About that, I want to reveal that a bit later
- Oh! Still a secret?
- So it's still a secret for this SHOWROOM?
- Still a secret?
- Well, some information has already been revealed
- That's right
Well, are you going to pursue challenges in new areas?
Or will you try to build on the activities you're currently doing?
- Your method of questioning is really good
- The way you asked that question was super good
- Thank you!
As expected, you haven't lost your touch
Your MC skills have not declined at all, both of you
Well you can talk about it abstractly
The truth is, I want to do a lot of things
So there isn't one thing that stands out now but
But I think many people like the singing and dancing sides of me
So I want to continue doing that
- Ah, so for the fans even after this...
- There will be many chances to meet Jurina
- That's right
- That will make them happy
So there's this, and also it'd be sad if there are no handshake events
That's why I'd like to do some events where fans can see me at a close distance
That's what I'm thinking
I won't be like "because I'm an actress I won't do fan events anymore"
I'm not going to be like that
- So you want to do your activities while being true to yourself
But yeah, I want Jurina to be like that
So it's like taking the bits of 48 group
The parts that are symbolic
So even if it's not a handshake event
It'd be great if the essence of "idols you can meet" can be retained
- Jurina has been in SKE more than half her life
- That's right
- So you're 22 now...
- I came in when I was 11
- So it will be exactly 12 years when you graduate
Isn't 12 years amazing?
It's one cycle of the zodiac
- That's amazing
- It's amazing
- Yabai
Ah, Maeda-shachou is here
Maeda-shachou?
- Maeda-shachou!
- The SHOWROOM CEO
- Ehhhh?
- Thank you for watching
I heard he's on a business trip right now
Thanks for watching while you're on your trip
I'd wanted him to come here
Thanks for watching from your trip
I'm in your care
I've had a fairly long history with SHOWROOM
In the beginning I really worked hard on the streams
I got something like an award for it
- You did your live concert recently too
- Yes my live concert too
They helped me out a lot
Is Akimoto-sensei watching, I wonder?
He might not know about it
He probably doesn't know
- Did you tell Akimoto-sensei directly?
I did tell him
Like "I'm about to make the announcement"
- What did Akimoto-sensei say?
- Ehhh?
- You can't say it?
- It's fine whether you reveal it or not
- "It's a new start for you isn't it?" something like that
"Good luck"
For Akimoto-sensei
Just like us, he's known Jurina since elementary school
- Akimoto-sensei must have felt like he raised you
- Like his own child
- He definitely feels that way
That's true
We have deep feelings about it too
To be able to see someone's life to this extent
It's usually only family
- Normally we wouldn't
- The fans too
I might have spent more time with fans than my own family
Members too, for a long time in SKE
I wonder if there's anything there
No comments?
- If you have any questions, please send them through
- "Where's Masana?" is written there
You're there aren't you?
- I'm here!
- We're recording only her voice
- Masana-san is naked right now so she can't come
With all the staff around here
You're kidding right?
- We can't broadcast someone naked on SHOWROOM so...
- The CEO is watching too
- We're sorry
"Did you tell Mariko-sama?" was written there
Ah, I did tell her
I even phoned her today
I said I'll work hard for the announcement
"Finally, otsukaresama" was what she said
Nakanishi how was your reaction when Jurina told you?
"Is that so..."
- I became melancholic
- Like a mother
How do i say this
It's not like watching her Seijin Shiki
Somehow I went, "Ah... is that so"
Like she's leaving the nest
- So you were melancholic?
- I was melancholic
Neesan was quite something
- "EEEHHHHHHHHHH" she went like that
- The message was full of "E"
That was the only alphabet I typed
I told Takamina-san too
- Oh!
Because she helped me out a lot, I told Takamina-san too
She said "is that so, you worked really hard"
Since you mentioned Takamina-san, things are getting replayed in my head
It's really nostalgic
Everyone's not around anymore
It's lonely
- The last of the 1st gens
- I was super lonely by myself
Everyone vanished
- "Vanished"?
- Your manner of speech...
But I've always thought that way
Definitely staying on is harder, I think
Yes that's right
She's always carried that burden
Up till now she's been SKE48's Jurina
From there, after graduation
She'll continue as Matsui Jurina on her own
I wonder what her feelings will be then
Tell me about it privately later
But I'm sure even if she did the same work her feelings would be different
Because there are lots of things I can't do when I'm an idol
When I think about all these restrictions going away
I can experience many different things and I'm looking forward to it
"What kind of graduation dress will you be wearing?"
I actually designed it myself
- I've drawn it out
- Isn't it a bit early?
Already?
Yeah, I wanted to draw it
- When I was on my hiatus
- Oh is that so?
- I wrote a bunch of lyrics too
- You're going to reveal that somewhere later
"It's about to hit 30 thousand"
Wow!
What's this? You all should have come when I did my live concert
It was around 20 thousand when I did the concert
"When did you start thinking about graduation?"
Around Masana's graduation
- That was way back!
- That was a long time ago
So when I heard about Masana's graduation
We were the only two 1st gens left
And when I thought "Oh I'm going to be alone now"
I thought maybe I should also start thinking about it
I'm sure you thought "I'm going to be next"
Even within the 1st gens
Because I get lonely easily
I thought it'd be impossible to do this alone
But when I heard of it from Masana
I thought I shouldn't make Masana sad or worried
I said "I understand" and didn't cry
But when I got home and was alone
I became super lonely
While crying I wrote lyrics for Masana
At that time I thought "I'm going to be next"
- So you thought about it a lot for a long time
- I thought about it a lot
But how do I say this
I'm not Masana, but I felt like I'd done everything
The various dreams I had in SKE were able to be realised
Really, that would have been impossible if I were alone
Because fans and members were there
They all came true
Next, I want to realise the dreams I'll have when I go solo
And you're still only 22
- That's right
- There's a lot I can still do
It's the age where I entered SKE
EHHH? YABAI
You could stay on for about 6 years
For me it was 7 years from here
Let's start working hard from today
- That's amazing Neesan
- Let's go back in now
You could still re-enter
You danced so well
It's true!
Amazing! I respect you!
Since you're here now you understand right? These feelings
I don't want to wear cute costumes
- I wore school uniforms for about 7 years from this point
- Yabee!
- Right?
- Yeah
- That's crazy
- Yep
- I respect you
Can you wear the Party costume now?
- From now on?
- Impossible! It's so tough
- Recently I wore the "Tsuyoki Mono Yo" costume
It was rough
It was so tight
- Don't say it's the last time
- It was so tight
- Let's wear Party together
This person is really eager to wear it
- She really wants to wear it
- Let's have only Nakanishi wear it if possible
Uh, what was it
How were the juniors' reactions?
- Donchan came right?
- She came
- She didn't make it in time for the announcement though
- She came just for this
- Yes, that was unfortunate
Also, the one who cried a lot was Miyomaru
Nomura Miyo-chan, she cried a lot
She's usually not a girl who shows her tears
So I was quite surprised
She's someone I pampered
So I was really happy
- Also Chika-chan's greeting was good wasn't it
- It was good!
She did it properly
It's one moment that makes me go
"Ah, Chikako has grown too"
"Since she left the countryside" something like that
Because she was a draft member for Team S
Can we say it's her growth
She's like the heaven-sent child of Team S
And things like that, like their growth
It triggered your decision to graduate
- Yes, that's really it
Even when I talked to Akimoto-sensei
I asked how I should time my graduation
He said "maybe when the members all grow up?"
"When the younger members come up"
"And you feel you can leave SKE to them"
"Surely you'll decide then," he said to me
At that time it didn't really register for me
But now that was certainly the thing that made me decide
It's not because I want to quit soon
Or that there was something I wanted to pursue
It's not those things
It's because I'm satisfied SKE will be fine even without me
And I can hand it over
It'll be alright even without 1st gens
Because that's what I felt
I thought that I must like SKE a lot
Yeah, that's right
- That's what I think
- I see
- Also from this moment
How many months do you have?
- Around half a year right?
- Yes I have about half a year
- From now on, during this period
Is there anything you want to convey?
But well, you've already said everything that needs to be said haven't you?
- Well, but...
- For the juniors, really
Jurina's absence is a big thing
When Neesan and Nishishi graduated
Through your absence
You hoped that members will develop a sense of crisis
And start working harder, that's what you told us
I remember that very clearly
For me, similarly
With all the 1st gen seniors gone
I hope everyone develops their awareness
And carry SKE together, with everyone
Not just one person
But for everyone to do it
I think it's good if everyone aims for the center position
So something in that vein, how do I say this
When it was just us 1st gens
Everyone was pretty competitive
- Ah that's right
- We were peers, standing on the same starting line
- There wasn't a sense of holding back for seniors
- That's right, there wasn't that sense of reservation
If it becomes like that
I really think SKE would be more interesting
By withdrawing from the group
It'd be good if they think "Ah, I want Jurina-san's position"
- So from here, SKE would become interesting
Even if Jurina has graduated
I do think it will become interesting
Well, I don't know what kind of scenery that will be
- That's right
- Jurina's presence is so big
- It will really become a new SKE
- Because we've never seen SKE without Jurina
- It will be reborn
- Gradually -- even the company has changed
I think it's changing to something new
Nao-chan was center, Suda-chan was center
Recently, I think it's gradually becoming a new SKE
That's being shown lately
For the sake of renewing the group
I really thought it might be better if I weren't around
- Oh, is that so
- Yeah
To completely renew SKE
For the... I don't know how many chapters it's been
I think I want them to do that
But also, there's also that
For Nogizaka, Maiyan announced her graduation
- I'm really, an idol fan
- For Keyaki, Hirate-chan also left
All the groups' centers are graduating
In 2020
The idol world... right?
- It's a storm
- It draws attention
That's what I think
I overlapped with them
It'll be quite a year
- Is there anything you want to do before the graduation?
Things I want to do before graduation?
Because the staff members are here I should say it right?
- Yeah, because everyone's watching
So I made this thing called J Family
So I gathered members who like me
There's 17 of us now
We can do a stage
- That's why...
- "Earlier you said you wanted to produce a stage" in the comments
- Yeah I want to do things like that
Before I realised it I've started looking at SKE from a producer's perspective
After being there for so long
I want to do that
If we do a J Family stage
I want to produce it
It'd be good if I can do activities in J Family too
- Certainly, for a produced stage
Those being produced are also likely to grow
I'm sure there's something to be gained there
- There definitely will be
But also
I also want to try producing a group
Oh you mean for a coupling track?
- No, I mean after I graduate
- A completely new group, right?
After graduation
- Milky is doing it right now too
- I also want to do producer-like things
- Like Sashihara-san
- Juri-P
- Juri-P??
- Because I'm also writing lyrics
I can teach them dancing too
I can do everything myself
That's why somehow
Rather than myself being popular
I think I want to make someone else shine
So I want to try producing
I want my own, how do I say this
I want someone to inherit my genes
I'm not giving birth yet though
I can't entrust this to my children
- The younger generation
- Yep yep
- I want to assemble a group and do it
- I really want to see it
- That's what I feel strongly right now
- I see, that is also a challenge
I've sung many songs written by Akimoto-sensei
I think he's amazing
His ability as a producer is great
Like, "this girl is like this, so let's make her sing this unit song"
Those parts are impressive
I think it's important for someone to inherit that from him
Because Akimoto-sensei's at a good age now
- He's at a good age now
- He's at a good age
I want to become someone
Who can be called the 2nd Akimoto Yasushi
I mean someday, someday, really someday
- Through various experiences
- That's right, I first want to do various things on my own
And only on top of that become something like that
I see
By the way, I dislike being written about like that by reporters
What...
I dislike it
It is troublesome
Someday I want to be like that, that's all
This is your youth
Finally blooming into something
If you had entered when you were 22
You would probably be living a normal life now
For us...
For us we're just normal housewives half of the time
- It's totally different, even our way of thinking
- It's different
I'd like to have that kind of life someday too
- You're kind of looking forward to it right?
- Yes! I'm really looking forward to it
- It's a positive graduation
- It's super positive
But Jurina also has most of her 20s ahead of her
- That's incredible
- You can do anything
I can still go on for about 10 years
You can totally do it
What.. what is it?
Let's go back to SKE once more
- After 10 years you can still be like us
- There's more than 35,000 now
Wow!!
There's actually something I'm really worried about...
- What is it?
I think there might be many fans who are depressed now
At this moment
There's this daifugo app for SKE
So in this app fans are working hard
For their oshimen
If you're number 1
You get to be the goodwill ambassador for Hawaii
It's an event like that
I applied to be a candidate
The reason is, because I've decided to graduate
There won't be a chance to battle like this with other members anymore
So I wanted to work together with my fans towards this
Because that kind of thing will decrease after this
That's why I wanted to do this
Normally even if there was something like this
I'd want to give it up for members who don't get many chances
Normally I wouldn't go for things like that
This time I'm super raring to go
I want fans to help me out
But I'm worried they're too depressed to play right now
It wouldn't be good if that were the case
- But by watching this SHOWROOM
- They might be at ease though
- I wonder? I'm worried
"I'll work hard" is written there
They really did comment that
This feeling of being positive
And the fact there will still be chances to meet you after graduation
It's good for fans to hear that from you
I want to create more memories with everyone
So I thought this daifugo thing would be a good one
- That's your declaration to create more memories until October
- Yes, I want to create lots of memories together
- There's already been heaps of memories up till now though
- There's 12 years worth of memories
Ah, the tweets
We're collecting messages with the hashtag #ArigatouJurina now
Shall we read some of them
- What did we do about this
- Oh the password...
Nobody is asking me about romance
Wait, you wanted questions about that?
- I mean...
- Everyone's laughing
I'll definitely be asked about it everywher
When Mayu-san graduated
And also when Sashihara-san graduated
In music shows they'd be asked
"The love ban is going to be lifted, right?"
They were asked a lot like that
When I appear on TV next time
I thought I might be asked like that too
- You throwing it out?
- No, I'm just thinking of how to answer at the moment
- On a later day
- You'll be asked about it somewhere
Yabai, the me who is sandwiched by other people's wives, also...
There's a weird excitement here
Because your anxiety was finally released
I'm really comfortable when the two of you are around
Yabai, it's just like the old times
- Just like old times
- Like your casual switch was flipped
Yeah, and Masana is watching too
It's reassuring
The staff members are also like, "this is the SKE we know"
The staff members told me that
- "I like Nagoya-ben"
- "We're working hard at daifugo"
- Mmm.. There's a bunch of melancholic ones too
- Because Jurina's been here since elementary school
There are comments saying they can't imagine her in love
"The fact that it's a positive announcement makes me the happiest"
- "I love that part about this"
- There's a cute illustration too
- "A positive Ojuri"
- Cute!
Wanna take a look too, Jurina?
"I'm depressed but I'll work hard at daifugo"
Sorry for making you sad
- Yesterday your mother was playing too wasn't she?
- Daifugo?
- That's right! My mother is J Mama in the game
Some fans played with my mother too
What a great app
- But really Nagoya-ben is really Jurina I feel
- It really comes out!
Either Kawamura Takashi* or Matsui Jurina
[*Nagoya's Mayor]
That's one hell of a comparison
I wonder if the viewers know him
"I'm happy that you announced it in the theatre"
Yeah definitely- HAHAHA
Isn't that Nakanishi's "Kisudame" footage
Who the heck uploaded this?
If you search #ArigatouJurina, you can see it too!
Stop it stop it!
I regret talking about it- STAHP IT
- STAHP IT STAHP IT
- That's so nostalgic
- I regret bringing that up myself
- The way I laughed was quite yabai
I want to see you do it again
Ah, "I'll miss you after graduation, but I'm not sad"
"I'm looking forward to Jurina's future activities"
We're all looking forward to the new Jurina
- It'll be a first to see Jurina who isn't an idol
- "Ikkimuchi is really fu-"
YABAI I'M SUPER FAT
- Yabai... Yabai!!!
- That's just the angle I think
Jurina... let's look at it after the end
- YABAIIIII AAHHHHH
- Let's look at it later
- YABAI YABAI YABAI YABAI
- I'm sure there were lots of better shots
- I'LL DEFINITELY LOSE WEIGHT BY SEPTEMBER!!!
- By the way, how many kilos do you weigh now?
OI!!!!!
Hush! Hush!
Masanaaa... Masana....
- I think you need to be quiet
- They were going to put the mic on her but
- The manager didn't think it was a good idea
- That was the correct judgement
FORTY EIGHT DESU
That was a lie
"Thanks for having been my sun"
I'll be your sun from now on too
Kimi no taiyou...
You're acting pretty weird, are you ok?
- Let's calm down
- I'm always like this though?
- Because Masana is here too
These are the members who went on the Okinawa trip together
The footage was at the endroll of the movie
The travel footage
Do you remember it?
That was our first movie
When I remember that
It's nostalgic
In "Bukiyou Taiyou"
- When we appeared in Kouhaku
- CHAMPION!
Sorry sorry
- This song I wrote while thinking about pro-wrestling
- I like the Jurina who likes pro-wrestling
- Really? Some of the wrestlers tweeted warm messages
- It made me happy
- After graduation are you going to do that kind of work too?
- Right now I'm doing some martial arts-related work
I get to go abroad too
It's an organisation called ONE Championship
I was appointed the ambassador for them
If you become a fighter I'll really support you
That would be impossible for me but
I'm doing a bit of kickboxing at the moment
- But Jurina really suits cool concepts
- I think this really suits her
- I'm happy to hear that
- I like sports
But for us we are kind of athletic idols at SKE aren't we?
- Yeah, SKE is kind of the athletic type
And my body is broken
- You need to take care
- I will
- It's a sprint till October
But, after you made the announcement
We probably had the deepest memories
It was really fun
I'd love for you to make many memories in this 6 months
It'll pass in no time at all
And also Jurina will definitely be
Pretty busy with graduation-related work
By the way, because I really like travel
I want to appear on travel TV shows
- Yes, let's request a bunch of things
- Please call me for a travel TV show
I want to be on things like Tokumitsu-san's show
- Like machibura*?
[*machibura = hanging around town]
- Yes, I want to machibura
And I also like Downtown's Hamada-san
I want to be on his show too
Let's at least request it
And of course, lots of Nagoya-based shows helped us out
For live performances, TV shows, etc.
So I want to be on Nagoya-based shows too
After graduation I want to be a regular in some Nagoya shows
- I'm really requesting a bunch of things
- Let's request all these things here
Also about handshake events
I may still do something like that after graduation sometimes but
My schedule on weekends will mostly be freed up
So when you think about that, being a regular is definitely possible
Sashihara-san said it too
When you're an idol there's a lot of work you can't do because of handshake events
Lots of things will be possible now
Amazing isn't it, there's too many comments
"The things you left behind will be taken over by your juniors"
"You've worked hard for a long time"
Happy to hear that
We're still collecting messages
#ArigatouJurina
And if you write something now
There's a high chance Jurina will read it
Now is the time to write them
She's literally reading the feed now
I'm not getting any sleep tonight
Wow this old pic, my chin was so sharp
This one's scary, I'm so fat
Earlier, from Jurina
We heard that we might do that concert
That means Satou needs to go on a diet too
Let's work hard towards that
Eh? There's only 15 minutes left?
- It went by so quickly
- Also if there are any questions please send them through
- Because the feed is scrolling too quickly, we might not be able to read all of them
- Ah, I'm so hungry
- I'm super hungry
- What about songs that you all want to hear at the graduation concert?
- Ah you mean to write them in?
- I'm not going to take those suggestions
- Because you've already decided on half the setlist
- I was kidding, I'll take suggestions
We want to create memories too don't we
While Jurina is still in SKE
Yes, if there's something we could do
Let's go on a trip
I want to go on a trip
- Like Okinawa
- We could even do it after graduation
At night we could do that psychological test
Do you all remember that?
If Jurina becomes the Hawaii goodwill ambassador
- To Hawaii
- Jurina-san, I'm in your care
Then the 1st gen oshis need to work hard too
Those who support all of us too
Even if you're not a Jurina-oshi, become one now for the game
- But really the fact that there are people commenting "Ikkimuchi"
It just plainly makes me happy
Because it's been over 5 years since we graduated
- 5 years, that went by quickly
- "You can't leave out Oogoe"
I did say Oogoe would be the first one
"I want to see Goshoku no niji"
Yeah I do want to sing "Goshoku no niji"
Jurina really remembers things
Like lyrics
Jurina has pretty incredible memory
- It's incredible
- She probably remembers lots of memories about fans
- Wonderful!
- Even without backing music you're hitting all the notes
"Kamigami no ryouiki" is also mentioned a lot there
It hit 40,000!
- Wow, more than 40,000
- Thank you! 40,000...
- About this, to hit 40,000 is quite something
When I first started doing this
It hit 40,000 and 50,000 pretty quickly
Even when streaming alone
There would be heaps of towers
There would be around 50,000
Recently though, it tops out at 20,000
But today there's 40,000 which is quite something
That's something to be happy about
Everyone wants to hear from Jurina
Some really nostalgic songs are written there
I want to do "Glory Days"
Glory Days...
Ah, "Will you assemble for Kamigami?"
- What's going on?
- Masana, what is it?
- When Jurina talked about the things she wants to do
The things you said here, were you serious?
The things I want to do?
You mentioned a few things
Ah, that's right, you're asking if I was serious?
Was I serious?
It needs to be said for real
But I can't say it for real, the things I want to do
Was there something?
What kind of thing is it?
I can't say it yet right now
- Ah so you're going to release information gradually?
- You'll make it a surprise?
- One after another
- For the sake of reporters worldwide
- Jurina's movements are like an ossan
- One after another
- Cheers~!
Like Jon Kabira-san
"It's good~"
[They're imitating Jon Kabira]
- Masana is really laughing
- Jurina gets weird when she's around 1st gens
- Why are the two of you here for such an important day
- I actually wanted to ask you that
Why did you choose the two of us?
At first the staff members told me
It'd be good to have your douki here, right?
And they asked "what about Masana?"
But Masana... I can't entrust this to her
If it were Masana...
Actually I want to talk about various topics
But if it's Masana, I'd end up taking over the MC duties
- That would definitely happen
- I'd be putting things together
And I'd have to work hard by myself
So for me to be at ease, I called Nishishi and Neesan
That's the correct decision
I thought it would have been interesting, but...
But people want to see you with Masana on SHOWROOM on other occasions right?
Yeah, let's do something
Around Grand Canyon*
[*In Sunshine Sakae, not the actual Grand Canyon]
That's nostalgic!
- With Ikkimuchi, again
- Graduating really opens up a lot of possibilities
- Eh?
- You kept saying you weren't coming on
I've put on my clothes now
She was naked
- What's with your naked character, seriously?
- I'm the Naked Director*
[*Go watch it on Netflix]
- Calm down, calm down
- Everyone, good evening! I'm Oya Masana!
That's nice, everyone's happy to see you
- You always do your self-introductions properly
- "WATASHI GA OYA MASANA DESU" you should do that
- You should do that
- That's nostalgic
- That was from the SSK, wasn't it
From Masana I guess we'd like to hear
How was it when you watched Jurina today?
= I thought she'd be more nervous
- Oh yes, yes
Yesterday I did voice training
- Voice training?
- I did voice training
- Weren't you with me?
For the song, it's actually playing in the background now
I wasn't able to sing* it properly so I did some voice training
[*This was in Nagoya-ben]
- Your Nagoya-ben is coming out
Yes, so during voice training
I was told "you need to relax to sing this"
If I'm nervous I'd go like "EEEEHH"
So I was told "that singing style is bad"
"It will actually hurt you, so you need to stop"
- I was told that, so I ended up being really relaxed
- So you created that feeling internally for the song
- It was probably better to sing first wasn't it?
- Yes, I think so
- If that weren't the case I might have cried
- Because they were lyrics I wrote myself
- Jurina has always been really serious about singing
- One thing that I really remembered was
At the Dome concert, Jurina did a solo song didn't she?
- Oogoe?
- At that time she asked me for advice on how to sing it well
I said, maybe be careful with what you drink
Drinking hot water might be good
And then on the concert day, backstage, she went
"WHERE IS MY HOT WATER?!?"
That's a good story
- That's a good side of her
- She was really drinking it
I was so proud that she took my advice
"She's really drinking it"
I really remembered that
She's always been serious about things like that
Today as well, for the announcement
I dyed my hair black
- Oh is that so?
- Up until then I was really playing with it
- Ah you mean your hair?
That's good
That side of you is good
But I actually wanted to do something intense as a twist
Like a fashionable type of grey but
But then I thought I needed to do the announcement properly
So I made it blackish
- But for Jurina there's been this image of her until the end
That image has seriously never changed much
So it feels like Akimoto-sensei's heaven sent child
- Kawattoran*?
[*Nagoya-ben for "unchanged"]
- Kawattoran?
- You didn't change, kawattoran!
What about your final day?
Lol the wire is dangling
- Maybe it can be orange?
- Look at this
- What was it, the final day?
- Your hair colour or style on the final day
- That's something for you to look forward to
- It's a secret?
- It would be surprising if you've already decided on that kind of thing
- No, I've actually already decided on it
- Really?
- Please look forward to it
- It's a SE-CRET*
[*She says "mihitsu" rather than the correct word "himitsu"]
(awkard silence)
- I don't get it
- She's returned to her old self
- I'm back
- Welcome back!
- Tadaimango~!
- You should say "Okaeringo"
- Seriously, today
It's too nostalgic today
- This Ikkimuchi talk is really something
- We didn't drink a drop of alcohol
- Not a single drop
- Mine is grapefruit juice
Should we all talk about our drinks?
The time we have left...
There isn't enough time
Masana do you have any other questions for Jurina?
Nothing in particular I think
Why the heck are you here then?
Why did you even come on?
- Because we meet often don't we?
We go eat meat a lot together
- We eat meat together
Yesterday, because we ate too much meat
- Neesan got angry at us
- I wasn't angry but
It's just like
That's so like Masana
In order to go have a meal with Masana
I need to remember, this is what eating with Masana is like
Speaking of meat, there's something that I really remembered
When I was 17- by the way this isn't a good memory
It's alright to talk about this right?
So we had some expensive meat
It got reported by tabloids
That was the first tabloid article about me by the way
Today we're talking about tabloids a lot
So at that time
This was written about Masana
That Masana is only friends with Jurina
In order to be treated to meat by Jurina
There was something like that
Masana was really depressed about it
- Because that wasn't true at all
I hope that wasn't true..
It wasn't true at all
Recently I was treated by her too but
"ARE YOU SURE IT'S OKAY?" was what she said
"ARE YOU SURE?"
I didn't say I would treat her but
"ARE YOU SUUUUUREEE?"
But that's not my aim
Because she's much younger than you
I have a memory about Jurina too
It's a proper memory
At a concert in Nagoya or somewhere
There was some onimanju in the sashiire*
[*Snacks to show appreciation]
I don't know if it was provided or if we bought it
It was in the dressing room
So those onimanju
When Jurina returned, it was gone
And Jurina got really angry about it
Hold on...
You worked with her for a really long time
Don't you have many memories?
Out of all of them you chose that?
I really like onimanju
- It's delicious
- I really like onimanju
- Was onimanju a Nagoya delicacy?
Yes it's Nagoya
- Everyone please try onimanju, it's really good
- But really back then for sashiire
It's like we should have it before Masana finishes them
- No way!
I also just remembered a sashiire story about Masana!
In the backstage of the theatre
There's would be many boxes right?
Masana would go
AAHH THE SASHIIRE IS HERE
But it was the box for mics and headsets
That's super funny
That's a good one
- A good episode
- What about being an onimanju ambassador?
- I want to become one!
After you graduate
Onimantaishi
That's strong
To all the onimanju companies
Definitely get in touch with Matsui Jurina
We'll be expecting your call
I'm funny today right?
It would be better if you didn't say it yourself
They'll be writing about it on Twitter
Nishishi is really strict about jokes
I tell dajare a lot, don't I?
And if the joke hits, I'd say the dajare again
And she'd get angry with me
"IT'S NOT FUNNY THE SECOND TIME AROUND"
- Nakanishi is stoic about that
- She's so stoic about jokes
- Are you going to do any dajare today?
You haven't done it in a while so it might be difficult
If there was a theme it might be better
Because onimanju is in our heads now
Nothing but that might come out
- What about making the theme "graduation"?
- Isn't that super difficult
It could be "Jurina" or "Ikkimuchi" too
I wonder if what would be good
Might be good to do one that conveys fun
Mata aimaSHOWROOM!
Wonderful
- "Graduation" is a really hard theme
Let's think of one
- I'm not a dajare type of person though
It's impossible
Please send some dajare in the #ArigatouJurina feed
"1st gen talk until the morning" is written there
I think we could do it
"Jurina memories"
"Jurina in Kataomoi Finally is too much of an ikemen"
"I love her in it"
- I totally get it
I was really boyish in it
I liked the MV too
I licked Rena-chan's finger
I kissed her ear too
How did you feel when you did those things?
- I like her, so...
- What kind of feelings...
- I like her so I felt like a boyfriend
- Because you like Rena?
- That's right, I like her
What's with that suspicious look?
You think I'm lying when I said I like her
- That's not it
But to complete Ikkimuchi, I think we should add Rena using CG
- That's right
- Please help us do that
Hope she texts me on LINE
There's 3 minutes left
Actually, I did something earlier without telling Jurina
You farted?
No!
I notified Rena-chan!
Eh? What?
- I notified her
- About what?
- Jurina's graduation announcement, immediately
- How did she reply?
- I don't know yet
- She might still be at work
Oh, because it's nearly time
- Do you want to do the announcements?
- Oh that's right! Nishishi do you have anything?
- Oh ah, Washi*?
[*First person pronoun that's more common with people 60+]
"Washi"?!
In Solid Cube I'm working as a motion actor
If you search Solid Cube on Twitter
You can see some information about my activities
Please follow it
What was that again? What cube?
Solid Cube
- Kamisoriddo cube
- What?
- It's coming out now
What about you Neesan?
Yes! Right now in Aichi prefecture
I'm working in an agency called Central Japan
I'll be doing a concert in March too
What will I do if 40,000 people come?
The seating capacity is only 300 though
I'll be releasing a CD too
If possible please also listen to it
Please also search for Satou Mieko
- Masana do you have anything?
- For me, I'll be appearing as a guest in some play
- What do you mean "some play"?
I don't know the details yet so please check it on Twitter
Is it already on Twitter?
Yes it's on Twitter but
It might not be updated, so...
- Anyway I'm putting this out there now
- Can you remember all your lines?
- I can't remember so I asked them to cut my lines
- I don't have any more announcements
What about repeating the details of the graduation concert?
Oh right
The graduation concert will be on 26 and 27 September for two days
The graduation theatre performance will be on 5 October on our 12th anniversary
Anything else you want to say?
It's great that you're having it on 5 October
- Ah what about the Shizuoka thing?
- Oh that's right, on 15 Feb
At the Ecopa Arena in Shizuoka there will be an SKE concert
I'll be appearing there as well
There aren't that many concerts left for me
So I'd be happy if you could come
So, after Valentine's...
Yes, so because of Valentine's
It will be a Valentine-themed show
Please look forward to it
Please do come!
I'll be waiting
I want to perform
Ah, please also tweet using #ArigatouJurina
We'll also be looking at them after this broadcast
So please keep sending them even after the broadcast
"There's Yokohama Arena too" -- yes that's right
Oh of course, please help me out with Daifugo too
Really for Jurina's graduation concert
I'm looking forward to it myself, as a fan
We'll see the curtain go down on a grand chapter
For us too
Just like how we participated in Maeda-san's graduation concert
I really felt like it was a great concert
I remember it even until now
I hope Jurina will have a legendary concert like that too
Ganbarunba!
Maybe it's good to wrap things up here
Yeah I guess so
Maybe you can say some words to the fans
I'm sorry for making this sudden announcement
And surprising you
There are 45 to 46 thousand viewers now
And having done this for nearly 12 years
I didn't expect to be able to continue to this point
It's not something I could have achieved on my own
It's because everyone helped me out
For the remaining.. 6? 7 months?
7 months? 8 months?
Within this time, there will be happy moments, and maybe tough moments too
I hope you'll lend me your strength and go through this together
I'm in your care until I graduate!
I'M HUNGRY
Well, thank you for watching until the end
Thanks to you all for coming here today too
There's a nostalgic feeling today but
- Please also support the current active members
- So kind!
- Let's have Jurina give the closing statements
- Okay, when I say "Oyasuminasai"
Let's go "1, 2" then "Mata aimaSHOWROOM" together
- Understood
If Jurina-san requests it, we'll do it
Minasan, GOOD NIGHT
One, two
MATA AIMASHOWROOM
Bye bye!
- Good night!