Everyone, good evening!
Matsui Jurina, first solo concert
~Without an audience, I sing only for you~
It has started! Yay!
It's been around a month since my last broadcast
Have you all been well?
There's no concert feel!
Because there's no response or reaction
There's no concert feel
It feels like a normal SHOWROOM broadcast
This is a concept where I deliver songs only for you
For SHOWROOM, how do I say this
I thought SHOWROOM was a way to do a concert
This is my first solo concert
By doing it in this form, I hoped many people would be able to watch it
That's why I wanted to do it in this manner
So this will be divided into two parts
The first will be a talk corner
The second part will be the live concert
I hope you will watch till the end
I can see you~!
How do I do this?
I can't carry this on my own
So for today
I invited a special guest
I'd like to introduce someone I actually get along very well with
Please come out!
It's Maruyama Rei-san~!
Hello!
-I will be intruding on you today
-Please have a seat
We're wearing matching clothes today
I'm Maruyama Rei! Nice to meet you!
It's kind of sexy, is it alright?
Matching is good but
In my case it's kind of shameless
-This one is in demand, but what the heck is this?
-You're in demand too
If you're wondering why she's so good at speaking
Although she's this cute, she's a comedian
-You look happy to be praised
-Not at all! I'm happy to be invited
How did we start getting along so well? Let's talk about the start of our relationship
That sounds like we're lovers
You have an impressive laughing style
-Are you okay?
-The start of our relationship was
-Girls Award!
That was spring last year
We did a live stream backstage
-You were the MC at the time
-That's right
After walking the runway Jurina-chan came backstage and that was when we met
But the truth is we're the same age
I was actually born and raised in a super countryside place in Hokkaido
At that time Jurina had debuted when she was in 5th grade
-6th grade
-Ah, 6th grade!
6th grade...
So I saw you who debuted in 6th grade
I thought "wow, what an amazing person"
You sweated a lot while dancing
-Was it "Oogoe Diamond"?
-My palms were sweaty too
Kya~ I'm sorry to all the fans!
-I touched her
-The music stopped for a moment there
That was ominous
So someone wonderful like her who's the same age as me debuted
I watched a lot of your videos on YouTube
I showed my classmates, "there's an amazing kid like this"
What left a huge impression was
Everyone was asked if they had confidence, or something, was that pre-debut?
Yes that was during a lesson
At that time everyone else was just like "ahhh..."
But Jurina was like "YES!"
The fact that you even know that is quite something
-The people who know about that...
-Your enthusiasm was really impressive
It's because I really did give it my all at the time
-But that was really cool
-I'm happy to hear that
-6th graders tend to give it their all don't they
-You didn't look like a 6th grader at all, you looked pretty mature
You're one to talk though
When we first met I thought there was no way we were the same age
I'm embarrassed
Why don't we look at the comments
"You're impersonating her"
Ah, looks like Maeda-shachou is here
Eh? Where?
Ah, it went up
Is he here?
He must be somewhere here
"Wow, a child genius"
"You're impersonating her"
"I know you! I've seen you before", thanks so much!
You should do an impression of someone
Of Jurina-chan?
-Wait, me..?
-Jurina-chan's running style
-You're making fun of me!
-No, I wasn't
Do it again?
Normally people would run like this, but Jurina-chan does it with her hands open
Because people actually do that in track and field
-They'd do that with their palms open
-You do that with your all you've got too, it's cool
-I actually impersonated you together with my classmates
-Do you want to speak by yourself today?
-No! That's not it, this is Jurina-chan's concert
-I'm going home!
-No wait!
We even have matching clothes today
-Yes, I bought them to bring here
-Thank you
-It's a present for you, please keep it for the memories
-Thank you!
-Sorry to all the fans
-I'm not going to wear this again, though
-That's awful
-That was a joke
You're terrifying
That was a joke!
You should do some tsukkomi!
Why are you responding so seriously
There's some dark elements there
Anyway, you released your album today right?
-Not today
-Oh, not today
-It's called "Privacy"?
-Yes, Privacy
-I've listened to it
-Thank you so much
Somehow it was very...
Ecchi!
-I went, "Eh? Was Matsui Jurina-chan like this?"
-You kept saying that backstage
That was a new experience
-But really, I'm quite a pervert
-Oh no! Is it alright to say that?
-Yes, it's fine
-Is she really a pervert? Let's take a survey here!
Those who think Matsui Jurina-chan is perverted please leave a comment
-Wait, we actually put in a survey yesterday
-Really?
Comments are fine too, though
"I know", "Yes", "You seem happy about it"
Lots of people going "Yes"
I think fans who come to handshake events know about it
-Oh really?
-If we're close...
-Why, does it get hot and sweaty or something?
-No, no
-Nothing like that right?
-No, I meant sometimes I play along
and respond to some of those jokes
-So you don't go "Ah!!", but actually respond
-Yes, even if they tell me those jokes
Even if they tell me such jokes I'd often play alo-
Why is your tongue out?!
I was worried about plaque on my teeth
So I licked it
Sorry
But at our meeting recently
Wow, my jokes are really hitting today, I'm happy
-That's why I called you, because you're funny
-I'm happy!
-Normally I wouldn't be this successful
-#$(*@#$#$#@
-$*#($*($*#($#
-People can't hear us if both of us speak!
-$#$#$&%*#&@
-$*#$&*$&@$*
-$*(#*%($%&@&*#&@ I'm gonna die
-Stay alive! From now on...
-Mom are you watching?
You're not listening to me at all
-Ahahahaha
We can't both be laughing at the same time
You should say something when I'm laughing
You're making quite a face there
-What's in the comments?
-So funny...
"You're not singing yet"
-Not yet
-We're keeping you in suspense
-Just a bit more
-Not yet
"You two make a good kombi"
Great, we did a good job!
You're not doing it at all
That's not a good kombi at all
Tomorrow I'll get beaten up when I leave the house
"Why didn't you do the high touch with our Jurina?"
I'm going to get killed
My tears are ruining my makeup
Ah, it's a fist bump
Your dark side is coming out here
-It's not a high five but a fist bump
-Yesterday, or the day before, I went to watch pro-wrestling
-It influenced you too much
-So these kinds of elements are coming out, let's do the elbow
Elbow high touch
That's new
This is fine right?
Yay!
We're probably the only ones laughing
-I wonder if that's alright?
-You're all laughing aren't you?
-Because it's without audience
-$#&$*#&$&*#$
-Ah, right without audience
-The staff members are here though
-Well yes, band members too
By the way, what's with the no-audience thing?
This experience is too new for me
Well I'm weird like that
I don't want to do ordinary things
Ah, you haven't changed
I haven't changed? How long have we known each other?
-She really doesn't change
-Were we classmates or something?
-Were we in the same school?
-We sat next to each other
-I threw my eraser at you
Usually boys and girls sit next to each other
-We wouldn't have sat next to each other
-Oh really? Boys next to girls?
-It wasn't like that for you?
-It wasn't.
-Girls and girls?
-That happened too
Eh? Because of the uneven numbers maybe?
-What's with girls and girls?
-High schools in big cities are really something
-City high schools
-Ah, really
Really, in Hokkaido...
I actually like Hokkaido
Eh, I'm happy!
Love love love
Rum? Love?
Love, not rum
Why don't you keep your normal cute face?
Because you're cute, so why are you making such weird faces?
I'm not cute!
When you came in didn't the makeup stylist say you didn't look like a comedian?
-Said "you're cute"
-That's embarrassing
You asked enthusiastically about my beauty salon
The makeup stylist was saying you look good today, hair and makeup too
And I asked if I could go too
I asked, "Can I at least go in for a treatment"?
-But you changed you hairstyle right?
-Yes
-I went with something like an ash colour
-Eh, recently it was red
Yes, red! But I didn't really spread the pictures around
So probably nobody knew about it
Sorry for looking at it
Also on SNS...ah the screen
I'll post it on SNS probably
-Your red hair? I think everyone wanted to see it
-You think so?
But this suits you too
Yes, we put in some highlights, my beautician worked hard
-There's curls and some highlights, I wonder if you can see them
-It looks good on you
It's really cute
But over here there's barely any...
-Oh we're going to hit 10,000 soon!
-It's happening!
Wow, it's true
About 400 to go
We're hitting 10,000 viewers soon!
-I'm happy
-You changed your hair frequently
My feelings change frequently too
But I think because my feelings change rapidly I can write lyrics
If I keep thinking about the same thing
Or thinking about the same person
-That's making me sound like a playboy
-It really does! Yabai!
Did you hear that? Everyone from Yahoo! News
That was quite something
They're gonna cherry pick this part to put in articles
No, I'm actually quite devoted
-Really?
-Yes.
Like, my favourite wrestlers remain the same
I like all of them though, I like people
-You like them while you like them, I'm sure?
-What do you mean?
When you're with someone you like, you're devoted but
After that, do you switch over to the other guy?
Ah, I may have hit a nerve
Did I hit the mark
But really, without experiencing various things I can't write lyrics
So I want to experience things so badly that I can barely hold it in
I see, I think that's good
You started in 6th grade
And you were an idol all this time right?
-There was a love ban in all those years?
-Yes, but actually nobody told me that there was a "love ban"
Even Akimoto-sensei said "I never said there is a love ban"
-Oh, really?
-Yeah
So I think I'm free to fall in love
You're cool
-Because you see...
-That's cool!
If there's someone cool
Well maybe not just cool, but someone who's kind, and you end up liking them
-Can you start hating them the next day?
-No, I can't
Right? Because we're human beings
Ah, I see
That's what I think
-You can use that in your lyric-writing
-I won't change my feelings if I love someone
My fans too, they have feelings of love for me
Similarly, I would fall in love with people too
-Because you're a human being
-Exactly, I'm a human being too!
That's what I want to declare
-Amazing, I'm in full agreement
-Full agreement?
-Thank you
-I think it's wonderful
-The Jiyuurina-chan who climbed up to where she is
"Jiyuurina-chan"??!
JIYUURINACHAN
For her to say she's also a human being, I'm of course totally persuaded
I'm all for it
So you said want to experience many things?
Wow, as expected you're ecchi!
That's misleading, wait...
-I need to stand for this
-But that's why you're ecchi, right
-Maybe not ecchi, but
-How many times are you going to say it?
But with various types of human love
Overflowing with these emotions you made this CD
Yes yes, that's right
-There was a lot I wrote from my imagination too
-The album jacket contains various aspects of Jurina-chan too, right?
-Yes, that's right
-I thought that was cute
-Those are mostly pictures I didn't really upload to SNS
-Because it's "Privacy" I tried arranging private pictures on that
-Ah, so those are pretty rare then
-Yep
There was one of nothing but my cleavage
Maybe I'm really ecchi
Look, she admitted it herself!
Everyone! This person admitted it herself!
I feel like we can go on forever
Maybe we'll just skip the concert?
Can we do just the talk tonight?
No, you have to sing
-I'll sing
-Everyone's looking forward to it
-Songs like "Sofa to Cushion"
-Ah yes yes!
You know it well
Yes, "Sofa to Cushion"
Anata to watashi wa
Sofa to Cushion
-You listened to it!
-Of course
-Your singing style is interesting
-SHOUFAWA TO CUSSHYEON!
SHOUUWA
Anyway I was really moved when I heard you wrote all of this yourself
Are you alright?
She's trembling
I think my fans are happy to see this
It's probably been a while since they've seen me laughing so hard
-Were you depressed or something? Are you okay?
-No, that's not what I meant
-Because I rarely crack up like this
-"I'm happy" was written in the comments
-Right?
They'd be happy to see me like this I think
I can't be like this with my members
Because we don't have members as funny as you
You're a pro
By the way, I was really looking forward to it so I listened to the CD
The staff is telling us to hurry up
-Sorry! We got carried away talking
-They said we can keep going for another five minutes
-Okay, got it
By the way, about "Sofa to Cushion"
Jurina-chan is the cushion, right?
Here's a question
Who is the sofa?!
Excuse me! Jurina-san!
I have one question!
-Who is your sofa?!
-You're noisy
Rei-chan!
Well, it's true that I'm big...
It's true that I am horizontally wide
Anyway, you didn't answer the question
You're protecting your idol image there
That's not true, there's many of them
-Eh?
-There's lots
You have many sofas?
-Many sofas, that's pretty yabai
-I do have many
Oh you mean, like it's not limited to people?
No I mean like my fans are also my sofas
Ah...
The staff members who always support me too
There are people who just make you feel at ease
Even among fans, there are types that make me feel at ease
And types that make it fun for me, many different types
So the type of people who make me feel at ease
They're the sofas
Basically people who support me when I need to lean on them
Right, so these are lyrics you wrote thinking of many people around you
I wanted a metaphor to describe the relationship between a man and a woman
So when I think about things that are always together
Sofas and cushions always come in a set
There aren't many houses with sofas but without cushions
So that's how I wrote "Sofa to Cushion"
That's cute!
But that's kind of like... burikko
-Eh?! Hold on...
-Well, it's really
-If you don't think like a burikko I think you can't write this
-Wait, no way
-Seriously?
-Well, normally...
"You're the sofa, I'm the cushion <3"
-Normally you can't say that right?
-You looked really cuddly
-Me?
-Yes
I'm gonna make you a hugging pillow
-On the bed..
-I'll cuddle
That's scary
-Don't take it so seriously
-But I thought there were lots of cute lyrics
-You're slouching, are you tired or something?
-No, it's my legs here
-Can I hold this?
-Yeah, go ahead
-I have a bent back, I've been going to the chiropractor
-I have a bent back too, let's do this together
-Oh! Did the viewership go up by 5000? It's now at 11,000
-Wow, thanks so much!
Oh it says here...
-"You two should do a regular SHOWROOM broadcast"
-That sounds like a great idea! Let's do it!
Maeda-shachou please help us out!
-It would be great if that happened
-It would be great if people watch it
Everyone at SHOWROOM please help us
Despite this being no-audience, I'm happy that I was invited as the MC
By the way in the CD
In your lyrics "Boku" appears a lot
-Did you write them from the perspective of a man?
-Yes! A male perspective
There are a lot of times where I think members are cute
At such moments I look at them from a male's perspective
Is that so?
-So you have something like a male switch?
-I like cute girls
Yes that's right
I love doing danso* too
(crossdressing as a male)
Fans too, if there are cute girls among them, I'd reach my hand out immediately
-So you'd go "Kya~ You're cute", something like that?
-Like "you're cute" then pat their head or pinch their cheeks
That's really like a man
There are sides of me like that
-You'll turn on that switch and write the lyrics?
-Yes, plus I'll pull out my feminine side too
And lay out some things I want men to say to me
For example, which songs?
Stay With Me
Stay With Me... is that the one with the rap?
-Yeah, there's a rap in there
-Was that you?
-Yep
-Ah, so that was you!
I was wondering who it was
-Eh, you can rap pretty well
-Really?
Also "Monochrome" is from a male's perspective too
"I want to protect you, I want to hold you"
"Just by looking at you my head is filled with your smile"
I want someone to tell me that
Ah, like that's your wish
We can see many sides of Jurina-chan in this album
It feels like I was stripped bare naked
-Like I'm not afraid of anything
-Kind of unexpected, but it's true you're a human being too
-I wondered if it was alright to expose yourself to this extent, although you're an idol?
-I exposed so many things
How long did it take you to write all this?
For this
For all of the songs, I did them gradually
Altogether about 9 were written within a month
-But actually there were 10 songs
-Wait, you wrote 9 songs in a month?
Yes, actually I can write one song in 30 minutes
Yabai!
You have great talent
After that, a person named Inoue Yoshimasa-san
helped me compose music to all those lyrics
That formed the mould
After that many fans told me, "You should definitely make a CD out of these songs"
And we actually showed that in SHOWROOM like this
And now you're having your first solo concert
I've also started using TikTok
It was started as part a campaign to promote this
In that account, the song you're hearing in the background now, "KMT Dance"
I wanted everyone to do the dance together
-I want to teach you the dance and do it together
-Eh? With me?
I want us to do it together later, do you want to practise it now?
Is it something you can do immediately?
Yes, it only needs your upper body
Is it still playing?
-I'll teach you once
-Okay
Kokoro mo odoru wa
Kamatte Dance
Kamatte Kamatte Kamatte Dance
Then a free pose
Ah, I understand the Kamatte Dance bit
-But, kokoro mo...
-Do it like this
Kokoro mo... It's like wakachiko wakachiko*
(*Google it)
Copyright Yutti-san*
(*A comedian, google him)
Kokoro mo odoru wa
Kamatte Dance
Kamatte Kamatte Kamatte Dance
YEAAAAH
-At the end you can do a pose that you like
-Understood
Kitai shiteru ne (I'll be expecting it)
-Eh? Tsukitei Housei? What?
-No, I said kitai
-Tsukitei Housei? What's with him suddenly? Do you like him?
-Kitai, I said kitai
Why?
There's phlegm in my throat now
Should I suck it out
-Can you be quiet for a minute
-Ah, sorry
-No, no
-We'll stop talking about Tsukitei Housei
-I said "kitai shiteru ne"
-Ah I get it now
-Can I live up to your expectations?
-I'll be expecting your final pose
-Understood
-We're gonna start
One, two
Kokoro mo odoru wa
Kamatte Dance
Kamatte Kamatte Kamatte Dance
I'm Tsuchiya Tao-chan
-I'm Tao
-You're making fun of her!
-No, I'm not!
One last time
I'm Tao
The voice sounds like her
Tsuchiya... Tao.... desu.
-Only the voice sounds like her
-Not the face?
-The face didn't look like her?
-I don't know what to say
It's crazy from the side, take a look
From the side...
You look so sharp
Sharp? Really?
Looks like a sculpture
Rather than Tao-chan, Jurina-chan might be better here I think
At the end I'll do Jurina-chan's running style
That might be better
I might have been overdoing it earlier
-Kamatte Dance, I'll do it like this!
-You have a strong heart
You have a strong heart. It's cool.
Elbow high touch
-Oh no, I have to go get ready now
-I'll do the Kamatte Dance while you're backstage
You can do some impressions too
-You can appeal to my fans
-Understood, I'm Maruyama Rei
Jurina-chan will be getting ready
Yes! I'll make preparations
I'm looking forward to it!
-I'll be supporting you!
-Thanks, I'll be back soon!
Itte kimasu
Icchatta ne (she's gone)
Anyway it's just me by myself now
What does everyone think about my talk with Jurina-chan?
Sorry to those of you who might be going "what's with this screen?"
Sorry, it's just me
Ah, there are some who watch my YouTube channel
Thank you!
So anyway, Jurina-chan and I are really the same age
The kids around me also thought that someone the same age as us becoming an idol was amazing
We watched many videos of her
Among those the one I impersonated was
"Is there anyone here with confidence?", "YES!"
That was Jurina-chan before her debut
That spirit was amazing to watch
I impersonated it
I'd never expected to do it in front of the person herself
I was surprised
We met for the first time at Girls Award
After the interview
We had a chat about all that
Then I uploaded a picture with Jurina-chan on Twitter
And then some fans told her "Rei-chan uploaded a picture of you"
That led to this offer
Actually I had meetings with Jurina-chan up till the start of this
She was always very kind
She explained the arrangements to me
I was really happy
"I went to Girls Award", thank you very much!
I'm grateful
These clothes too, Jurina-chan said let's wear matching ones
and do something like a girls room, or a girls talk
And I went "I'M IN FULL AGREEMENT"
"Those tuning in now will be surprised"
Akiyama-san
Actually I can do an impression of Robert's Akiyama-san
I'm Robert's Akiyama
Sesshiyasui~!
This SHOWROOM thing, it's a small place, but it's big
Jurina-chan is a really good girl
The concert is about to start right
"What are you showing us?"
Don't say things like that!
It's lonely!
Thank you
Anyway we seem to have a bit of time
I did this earlier but I'll do a face-only impression
I'll do a Kimura Tae-san impression
Does it look like her?
By the way I'm not drunk
"Whose solo concert is this?"
"It was good"
Oh nice to hear that
Thank you
"Please extend the broadcast", thank you
"I can't unsee Robert's Akiyama-san anymore"
I'm sorry
Jurina-chan's performance will start soon
I hope everyone looks forward to it
Personally, I was curious who did the rap for Stay With Me
I was surprised to hear she did the rap herself
Wasn't she really good at rapping?
Those who have listened to the CD, what are your impressions?
Let's share while waiting
It was good right?
And to start off the CD with Sofa to Cushion
It's really like Jurina-chan
It was cute right?
Earlier backstage she mentioned everything needs to be perfect
It's the Matsui Jurina we know, she's the same even backstage
She does anything well
"The low voice was impressive", yes there were songs like that
"I thought Jurina became fat"
Hi, I'm Jurina!
That was a lie, sorry
Please don't blame me tomorrow
"Do the running thing"
Jurina-chan mentioned this earlier but
Jurina-chan might have been in the track and field club
So she knew too much about the details about, what was it?
Like a fitness test?
I'm not sure
Running like that really left an impression
"Yes, this running style"
That's right
That image was too strong, that I actually did that when we first met
I'm sorry
"I love the both of you", thank you very much!
"Thanks for making Jurina-chan laugh", not at all
Jurina-chan took a lot of care for me, I was very happy
To be able to work together like this, this time...
Thinking of people in my generation... I debuted when I was 18
There weren't many entertainers who debuted at the same time who were 18 years old
But because there's Jurina-chan who's in my generation
I thought she was cool, then we met at Girls Award
So happy about it
There aren't that many, right?
There's Shirai Kenzou-kun, the gymnast
And then, people born in 1996 or 1997
By the way I was born on 1 April 1997
That's the last day for hayaumare*
(*Born between 1 Jan and 1 April)
So I barely made it into this generation
Happy to be called by Jurina-chan who is in this generation
"Jurina-chan has quick feet!"
Yes, yes
"Are you Tao-chan?" -- yes!
I'm Tao
This face
I don't understand it myself, why it looks like her
If I make my eyes into double eyelids, and make my mouth square
I'm Tao!
Something like that
Comments saying "good work on the opening"
Thank you
Yes, I'd be happy to work together again, thank you
There's 14,000 viewers now, 14,628 to be exact
That's great
"It's the Golden Generation" -- thank you
"You're funny, but let's go to Jurina-chan's performance now"
I'm sorry! Please bear with me for a little longer
"It's my birthday tomorrow so it's great to see your smile"
Jurina-chan will be happy to see these comments
It's great
"That looks like a face from a horror game stream" -- this one?
Did it appear? AAHHH! Like that?
"Jurina is a good girl" -- yes, that's right
Thanks for the many comments
We'll still be continuing, so please keep watching
I think it's time to go to the performance
But before that, please watch this VTR!
G-g-good evening everyone!
To liven things up for the performance
For the songs "YOLO" and "Chuu yori kiss"
Here's a lesson to liven things up
Mu, mu, mu
Mu-mu-music
S-s-start!
Something like that
M-m-moving on
Chuu yori Kiss
M-m-m-music s-s-start!
That's all folks, please enjoy the show
This was Matsui Jurina
This is Jurina by the way, I'm Jurina
I'm Jurina, I'm Jurina
This was Jurina
Tsuitekitai yatsu dake, tsuite koi!
Futsuu iiko majimena ko
Sonna no kyoumi nanka nee
Tama niwa hamehazushitatte ii daro
Sore ga jinsei te yatsu da
Ichidokiri shika nee no sa
Koukai nanka suru monka!!
Maji tsumannee maji kudaranee
Sonna hibi wa good bye (good night)
Maji omoshiree maji kakkee
Mirai wo egaite yukou
Kono yo ni umaretekita kara niwa
Ippun ichibyou mo muda ni suru na yo
Fuan mo kyoufu mo nigiritsubuse yo
Tsuitekitai yatsu dake tsuite koi
IYAOO
Oya ni otona erai sensei
Koitsura ni nagasarerunjanee
Jibun no michi wa jibun de kimeyou
Sore ga jinsei tte yatsu da
Ichido kiri shika nee no sa
Dare ni mo jama wa saseru monka!!
Maji de saikou maji de saizen
Sou omottamon kachi sa (champion)
Maji de saitei maji saiaku
Nani iwareta to shitemo
Kono yo ni umaretekita kara niwa
Ippun ichibyou mo muda ni suru na yo
Fuan mo kyoufu mo nigiritsubuse yo
Tsuitekitai yatsu dake tsuite koi
IYAOO
Please allow me to introduce the band members
First, Kazu on drums!
Bass, Shou-chan!
Goro-chan on the keys!
And lastly, Nacchan on the guitar!
We are one!
With this one team, let's go!
To the end, yoroshiku ne!
One, two
YOLO YOLO Yoroshiku ne
(YOLO YOLO Yoroshiku ne)
Y.O.L.O. Yoroshiku ne
(Y.O.L.O. Yoroshiku ne)
YO (YO) LO (LO) Jinsei tatta ichido kiri
YEHHHH!!!!
Kono yo ni umaretekita kara ni wa
Ippun ichibyou mo muda ni suru na yo
Fuan mo kyoufu mo nigiritsubuse yo
Sore sore sore sore
Tsuitekitai yatsu dake tsuite koi
IYAOOO
Adios!
THANK YOU!
Thank you!
That was the first song, we started off with YOLO
It feels like we've just played our final song
Please let me take a rest and have some water
Shou-chan the bassist will do the talk
Nandeyanen!
-Nandeyanen!
-Nice tsukkomi
That was my first time speaking Kansai-ben
That was one of our lively members
I'm already pretty tired! Yabai!
Is it alright? I'm worried if we can do it till the end
I'm gonna take deep breaths
I will receive your power, and do my best until the end
After livening things up with YOLO
Next, we'll do a feminine, and cute song
Please listen to it
Aishiteru
Konna ni mainichi dokidoki shitetara
Shinzou ga motanai yo
Anata wo omou to shizen to egao ni
Tsurai koto wasurareru
Koi tte fushigi ne
Aishiteru
Ima sugu kikasete anata kara
Me wo mite tsutaete
Suki ja naku   Aishiteru
Daisuki demo naku   Aishiteru
Konna ni mainichi dokidoki suru no wa
Watashi dake nano kana
Ichinichi anata no koe ga kikenai to
Shinpai ni natte shimau
Koi tte fuan ne    Koi tte fuan ne
Aishiteru
Ima sugu kikasete anata kara
Me wo mite tsutaete
Suki ja naku    Aishiteru
Daisuki demo naku    Aishiteru
Meeru wo suru sono tabi ni
Denwa wo suru sono tabi ni
Anata ni au sono tabi ni
Kimochi takamaru fukuramu bakari
Meeru wo suru sono tabi ni
Denwa wo suru sono tabi ni
Anata ni au sono tabi ni
Kimochi takamaru fukuramu bakari
Tawai mo nai yo na koto bakari
Anata kuchi ni suru kedo
Naze ni daiji na kokoro wa
Oku ni kakusu no
Aishiteru
Ima sugu kikasete anata kara
Me wo mite tsutaete
Suki ja naku
Aishiteru
Ima sugu kikasete anata kara
Me wo mite tsutaete
Suki ja naku
Aishiteyo
Daisuki demo naku
Thank you very much
Okay
Moving on
Earlier we mentioned this in the talk corner
It's a song written from the perspective of a man
I'd like to perform that song next
It's totally different compared to the song we just performed, "Aishiteru"
I hope you will compare the songs while listening
I put in some words I want to hear from a guy
Please listen to it
Stay With Me
Mujaki ni waratteru kao mo
Okotte suneteiru kao mo
Subete ga itooshiku kuruoshikute
Doushiyou mo nai kurai ni boku komaraseru
Kono mama kimi wo tsuresaritakunaru yo
Dare ni mo ubawarenai you ni boku no ude no naka
Sou itai kurai ni dakishimeteitaiyo
Zenbu mou boku no mono
Stay with me
Tsukarete nemusou na kao mo
Amaete motometeru kao mo
Subete ga itooshiku kuruoshikute
Doushiyou mo nai kurai ni boku komaraseru
Kono mama kimi wo tsuresaritakunaru yo
Dare ni mo ubawarenai you ni boku no ude no naka
Sou itai kurai ni dakishimeteitaiyo
Zenbu mou boku no mono
Stay with me
Just wanna stay
I wanna stay with you
Kono mama kimi wo tsuresatte shimaou
Dare ni mo ubawarenai you ni boku no ude no naka
Sou itai kurai ni dakishime hanasanai
Zenbu mou boku no mono
Stay with me
Just wanna stay
I wanna stay with you
Thank you
Moving on
It's quite sad but
I'd like to sing a song about farewells
To me farewells are...
Like members' graduations
I might end up tearing up talking about this
Members' graduations are probably the saddest farewells
No matter which member it is
It's like a hole opens up in my heart
Especially when my genmates graduated
I was very sad
Actually within SKE
There is nobody left in my generation
There's nobody who remained till now
It's pretty lonely that there's nobody to share this with
I took the feelings I have in such moments
And put them in lyrics
I hope you watching this now
Will think of important people to you while listening to this
At all times
You reached out your hand, so that I can be here
Thank you very much
I'd like to sing this song with these feelings of gratitude
Please listen to it
Anata no te
This is a special acoustic version for today
Anna ni tanoshikatta no ni
Ureshikatta no ni
Doushite darou? Konna ni mo kurushii no wa
Ima dake datte
Daijoubu datte
Nando tonaeta ka
Ano toki sashinobete kureta
Ano yasashisa ippai no anata no te
Ima demo wasurerarenai
Itsuka wakareru hi ga kuru koto
Wakatteita hazu nanoni
Doushite
Oboeteiru
Anata no te no nukumori
Ima demo
Shikkari nigitteita no ni
Tsuyokatta no ni
Doushite darou konna ni mo tooi no wa
Hanasanaiyo tte
Hanashitakunai tte
Nando ittetaka....
Ano toki sashinobete kureta
Ano yasashisa ippai no anata no te
Ima demo wasurerarenai
Itsuka wakareru hi ga kuru koto
Wakatteita hazu nanoni
Doushite
Oboeteiru anata no te no nukumori
Kotoba ni dekinakatta arigatou wo
Ima wa tada kamishimeteiru dake
Ano toki hisashinobete kureta
Ano yasashisa ippai no anata no te
Ima demo wasurerarenai
Itsuka wakareru hi ga kuru koto
Wakatteita hazu nanoni
Doushite
Oboeteiru
Anata no te no nukumori
Ima demo
Thank you
I don't sing this kind of songs when I'm in the group
Furthermore these are lyrics I wrote myself
I got emotional for a moment
And at a very good part of the song I teared up and my voice broke
So embarrassing
But I guess it adds a human element, so it's alright
So embarrassed
To be able to sing a song I wrote myself
The band members were willing to be a team with me
And perform together
Thinking about that suddenly reality hits me
Various aspects of this is touching
I want to sing tens and hundreds of songs but
Our lovely time is coming to an end
The next song will be the last
Ehhh?
Wait a minute, didn't we agree to do this?
Didn't we agree to say "ehhh?"
Can something like that happen?
-We got nervous
-None of you did it
But that's because everyone's deeply absorbed right?
Everyone's nodding
They were deeply absorbed in making this a good show
The final song
Is a song where you can make more and more noise
I'd like to sing it
You may have seen the odd video earlier
So I'm sure you can do the cheering call too
Are you going to make some noise!!!
Are you going to make more noise!!!
Thank you very much!
Please listen to it
Chuu yori Kiss!
Chuu yori kiss    chuu yori kiss
Hoppe ni chuu ja monotarinai
Otoko rashisa ga mitai no
Sore tte ikenai koto desu ka?
Anata wa itsumo watashi no koto
Kodomo atsukai
Mawari ga omotteru yori
Otono nano
Katte ni kimetsukenai de yo
Imouto da nante
Watashi wa cute ja nakute sexy nano
Amai okashi dake ja dame yo
Manzoku nanka shinai wa
Ima sugu dakiyosete
Ubatte yo
Chu chu chu chu
Chuu yori kiss    chuu yori kiss
Hoppe ni chuu ja monotarinai
Otoko rashisa ga mitai no
Sore tte ikenai koto desu ka?
Chuu yori kiss    chuu yori kiss
Odeko ni chuu ja monotarinai
Onna ni umaretanda mono
Dokidoki shinakya monotarinai
Anata wa shoushinmono nano ne
Aizu shiteiru ja nai
Mawari wa watashi yori saki wo
Itteru no
Ano ko wa toshiue kareshi to
Mayonaka doraibu
Kono ko wa kata dakare nagara
Irumineeshon
Hayaku shitai
Asetteiru
Sukoshi wa kimochi wakatte
Otona no kaidan wo
Noborasete
Chu chu chu chu
Chuu yori kiss    chuu yori kiss
Hoppe ni chuu ja monotarinai
Tama ni wa shigeki ga hoshii no
Sore tte ikenai koto desu ka?
Chuu yori kiss    chuu yori kiss
Odeko ni chuu ja monotarinai
Aishiatteirunda mono
No to wa ienai hazu deshou!
Motometeru no wa
Yasashisa nanka ja nai
Honnou no mama no sugata
Hadaka no mama no sugata
Chuu yori kiss    chuu yori kiss
Hoppe ni chuu ja monotarinai
Otoko rashisa ga mitai no
Sore tte ikenai koto desu ka?
Chuu yori kiss    chuu yori kiss
Odeko ni chuu ja monotarinai
Onna ni umaretanda mono
Dokidoki shinakya monotarinai
LAST!!!
Chuu yori kiss    chuu yori kiss
Thank you!
I sang it all!
I'm tired!
-Rei-chan!
-Well done!!!
Amazing!
It was really good!
-Thank you!
-High fives all around
-It was amazing
-Thank you!!
Thank you!
ENCORE! ENCORE!
-ENCORE!
-I didn't prepare one, please stop
-I really don't have one so I'll be in trouble
-I wanted to say it because it was great, Jurina-chan
Well done!
I put too much emotion into it that I sucked at singing
Not at all!
I was better in the rehearsal! I'm disappointed!
While you were singing the viewership went over 21,000
Yay! Thank you so much!
I'm happy
For over 20,000 people to watch this
That feels good
-What are you touching?
-No, that's not it
Wow
-You're even pressing your chest
-Rei-chan thanks for watching until the end
No, it was great
In the middle, there were comments saying it's a music fair
-Even the backdrop was done so cute
-That's right, as expected of SHOWROOM
It's amazing, that's one of the reasons I chose this venue
That's one of the highlights, I'm really thankful to the staff
It's so flashy
It's thanks to the efforts of so many people that I would be able to do this
To do a solo
I've always been in a group so it always felt like everyone's here
-But because it's my first solo concert
-Yeah, it's unexpected isn't it?
-How was it? Do you have a sense of accomplishment now?
-It feels great to do this for the first time
That's great
I aimed for this actually
Aimed for what? To feel good?
Yes, to feel good, it's alright
-In an erotic way?
-It's fine let's drop it
-Sorry I didn't understand
-I'm sorry too
Everyone's "encore" call is not stopping
I'm happy! But really from now on I want to keep doing solo concerts
You did so well here without an audience
You're gonna do one with audience next?
Would Rei-chan come if I invite you?
Definitely, I'd love to come
Do come!
Eh, the next one will be with audience?
Yes, there will be
It would've been great if we could announce it here but
It probably won't go that smoothly
But if the concert this time is popular, it will definitely help in leading to the next one
I'm really thankful that so many people came to watch. Thank you!
It was a really good concert
Well done!
-Before you sang "Anata no te" it was already...
-Meat bun?
-"Anata no te nikuman"?
-No, no...
-"Anata no te ni iku mae ni" -- ah this is the meat bun?
How much of a fatass do you think I am?
So cute
I don't really want this to end but
The song "Ano hi kawashita yakusoku" is coming on at the right time
-It's a song telling us to quickly go back home
-Not at all
It's the perfect song to use as the ending
Ah yes, the last song
The song you can use to make an exit
Because it's "Ano hi kawashita yakusoku" (The Promise We Made That Day)
Right here, let's make a promise to have our next solo concert
-Ah, everyone please do the pinky promise in front of your screens
-Let's promise!
Next time, we'll do one with audience
I'll sing in front of your eyes! I promise!
Yubikiri genman, uso tsuitara hari senbon nomasu
Pinky promise!
We sealed the promise!
-DEFINITELY DON'T FORGET IT OKAY
-That's scary!
-DEFINITELY DON'T FORGET
-There are people like this
CAN YOU DRINK NEEDLES
There are actually people like that
Alright let's wrap it up here, we can continue our talk backstage
While eating crepes
-Seriously, well done!
-Thank you, thanks to the band members too!
Okay
Mata OaishimaSHOWROOM!
-That was a good one
Bye bye!